<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CloudOps Press on CloudOps</title>
    <link>/cloudops-press/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CloudOps Press on CloudOps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/cloudops-press/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of The Financial Times The Americas’ Fastest Growing Companies in 2020</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-named-one-of-the-financial-times-the-americas-fastest-growing-companies-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-named-one-of-the-financial-times-the-americas-fastest-growing-companies-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, Quebec, April 8th 2020 — CloudOps has been recognized as part of The Financial Times inaugural list of The Americas’ Fastest Growing Companies 2020. This prestigious award is presented by The Financial Times and Statista Inc., the world-leading statistics portal and industry ranking provider.
The FT The Americas’ Fastest Growing Companies is comprised of enterprises that have contributed most heavily to economic growth. 500 companies are featured on the list, which was announced online on April 6, 2020 and can currently be viewed on this page of the FT website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps’ Commitment to Enhance Your Business Throughout COVID-19</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/press-release-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/press-release-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>To our customers, partners, users, and friends,
As the global COVID-19 outbreak continues to evolve, we want to share the steps CloudOps is taking to help ensure the well-being of our employees and communities, as well as the continuity of our business.
We know that CloudOps has an important role in your business — whether that’s through product and service delivery or events, training, support, and consulting. Although we don’t foresee any interruptions to our core business operations, we are actively enhancing services to support an increase in customer demand for cloud services, including virtual desktops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of Canada’s Top Growing Companies.</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-growing-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-growing-companies/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to announce it placed No. 294 on the inaugural Report on Business ranking of Canada’s Top Growing Companies.
Launched in 2019, the Canada’s Top Growing Companies ranking program aims to celebrate entrepreneurial achievement in Canada by identifying and amplifying the success of growth-minded, independent businesses in Canada.&amp;nbsp;
Canada’s Top Growing Companies ranks Canadian companies on three-year revenue growth. CloudOps earned its spot with three-year growth of 96%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of Canada’s Top ICT Companies in 2019 by Branham300</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-ict-companies-in-2019-by-branham300/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-ict-companies-in-2019-by-branham300/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to have placed 191st in the Branham300 list of Top 250 Canadian ICT companies in 2019. This is the fourth consecutive year that CloudOps has been listed in this ranking. CloudOps was listed 197th in the 2018 Branham300 ranking.
The Branham300 ranking is based on revenue and consists of Canada’s most profitable, public and private technology companies. All Top 250 companies demonstrate significant revenue growth and altogether represent over half of the nation’s ICT (Information and Communications Technology) sector revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is an AWS Advanced Consulting Member</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-an-aws-advanced-consulting-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-an-aws-advanced-consulting-member/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to become an Advanced member of the AWS Partner Network (APN). As a consulting partner of AWS, CloudOps helps companies build or expand their businesses in AWS’ public cloud offering.
As the most mature cloud offering, AWS offers users a vast array of rich features from which to take full advantage of what the cloud has to offer. CloudOps’ membership speaks to the in-depth knowledge that our teams have with regards to AWS as well as our commitment to helping organizations transform digitally, building their businesses in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is in the Top 100 Cloud Solution Providers in Canada</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-in-the-top-100-cloud-solution-providers-in-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-in-the-top-100-cloud-solution-providers-in-canada/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to join the Top 100 (cloud) Solution Providers in Canada for Channel Daily News (CDN), owned by IT World Canada. CloudOps has been listed as the 91st solution provider in Canada and was one of eight newcomers to the list.
This ranking comes from data collected by CDN from IT solution providers across Canada. It produces an industry benchmark report that sheds light on industry trends. The results were announced at the Top 100 Solution Providers Gala last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Microsoft DevOps Competency Partner</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-microsoft-devops-competency-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-microsoft-devops-competency-partner/</guid>
      <description>The Microsoft Competency Program gives partners the opportunity to demonstrate proven expertise in delivering quality solutions to specialized areas of business. Partners reach competency in given areas through a skills assessment, in which they pass exams to demonstrate product knowledge, or through proving an ability to meet performance goals.
Today, CloudOps announces its completion of the Microsoft DevOps Competency. As a DevOps partner, CloudOps has proven its expertise in helping organizations modernize their application development approaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Stevens is a Member of the Apache Software Foundation</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/will-stevens-is-a-member-of-the-apache-software-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/will-stevens-is-a-member-of-the-apache-software-foundation/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps’ Chief Technology Officer, Will Stevens, has recently become a member of the Apache Software Foundation (ASF). He will continue encouraging the open source community and contributing to ASF projects.
The ASF is a charitable organization devoted to supporting open source software projects by nurturing communities, encouraging the development of quality code, and generating awareness of its member projects. The ASF was established in 1999 and is funded by donations and managed by volunteers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maddison Long accepted into Forbes Technology Council</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/maddison-long-accepted-into-forbes-technology-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/maddison-long-accepted-into-forbes-technology-council/</guid>
      <description>Maddison Long, Vice President of Products at CloudOps, a leading Canadian cloud consulting and services company focused on open source, cloud platforms, networking and DevOps, has been accepted into Forbes Technology Council, an invitation-only community for world-class CIOs, CTOs, and technology executives.
Maddison Long was vetted and selected by a review committee based on the depth and diversity of his experience. Criteria for acceptance include a track record of successfully impacting business growth metrics, as well as personal and professional achievements and honors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Red Hat Application Platform Partner</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-red-hat-application-platform-partner-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-red-hat-application-platform-partner-initiative/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to become a member of the Red Hat Application Platform Partner Initiative (APP). Consisting of partners focused on application platforms with emerging technologies, the APP Initiative encourages deeper collaboration between Red Hat and its partners in helping organizations modernise their application platforms.
Red Hat OpenShift unites developers and IT operations on a single Kubernetes platform to build, deploy, and manage containerized applications in any public, private, or hybrid cloud environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps listed in the Branham300 in 2018</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-listed-in-the-branham300-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-listed-in-the-branham300-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to be listed in the Branham300 Top 250 companies in 2018&amp;nbsp;for the third consecutive year. CloudOps has been listed as the 197th company, up from last year. Consisting of Canada’s most profitable, public and private technology companies, the ranking is based on revenue. All Top 250 companies have demonstrated significant revenue growth in every year since 2009, and altogether they represent over half of the nation’s ICT (Information and Communications Technology) sector revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Now a Kubernetes Training Partner</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-now-a-kubernetes-training-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-now-a-kubernetes-training-partner/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is happy to announce membership of the newly-founded Kubernetes Training Partner (KTP) program. Run by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), the KTP program focuses on furthering the educational efforts of Kubernetes Certified Service Providers (KCSP). CloudOps provides support, consulting, professional services, as well as training for organizations seeking to embrace cloud native solutions. As Dan Kohn, Executive Director of CNCF said:
“CloudOps has demonstrated a deep knowledge of Kubernetes, as well as noteworthy community initiative around cloud native technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Member of the Linux Foundation, the LFN, and the CNCF</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-linux-foundation-the-lfn-and-the-cncf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-linux-foundation-the-lfn-and-the-cncf/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps has always believed that open source software plays an important role in any cloud-based solution. By leveraging the power of community, open source projects transcend the incumbent industry players to act as a catalyst for transformation. The Linux Foundation and its subsidiary foundations provide sustainable ecosystems for these communities to grow and flourish. As a member of The Linux Foundation, the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), and The LFNetworking Fund (LFN), CloudOps is proud of its commitment to open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Kubernetes Certified Service Provider</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-kubernetes-certified-service-provider/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-is-a-kubernetes-certified-service-provider/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to announce that we are now a Kubernetes Certified Service Provider (KCSP). Run by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation in collaboration with the Linux Foundation, the KCSP program is comprised of 28 vetted service providers with substantial experience helping enterprises adopt Kubernetes successfully. KCSP partners provide support, consulting, and professional services and training for organizations seeking to embrace container solutions. As the only partner in Canada, CloudOps works with partners internationally, and with the CNCF to create a strong and vibrant Kubernetes culture that supports an array of complementary platforms, and fosters the community built around it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Ranks No. 305 on the 2017 PROFIT 500</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ranks-305-on-2017-profit-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ranks-305-on-2017-profit-500/</guid>
      <description>– Canadian Business unveils 29th annual list of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies –
Montreal, QC (September 14, 2017) Canadian Business and PROFIT today ranked CloudOps No. 305 on the 29th annual PROFIT 500, the definitive ranking of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies. Published in the October issue of MacClean’s magazine and at CanadianBusiness.com, the PROFIT 500 ranks Canadian businesses by their five-year revenue growth.
CloudOps made the 2017 PROFIT 500 list with five-year revenue growth of 193%, up from position 356 from last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership with NetApp Propels CloudMC and cloud.ca</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/partnership-with-netapp-propels-cloudmc-and-cloud-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/partnership-with-netapp-propels-cloudmc-and-cloud-ca/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce that CloudOps and NetApp have solidified a partnership that will provide all-flash, multi-tiered storage for our IaaS portal, CloudMC. CloudMC is CloudOps’ software for productizing and delivering cloud resources for telcos and shared services providers. The goal of having such high quality storage as part of our solution is to facilitate scalability, performance, and QoS for organizations leveraging CloudMC to monetize their cloud offering. The key advantages are APIs and automation to make the integration rapid and seamless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Certified as a Remarkable Employer</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-certified-as-a-remarkable-employer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-certified-as-a-remarkable-employer/</guid>
      <description>As CloudOps grows and matures as a business we look for ways to measure employee satisfaction, both as a means to understand the needs of the people who work here and as a means of comparison with the wider industry. To this end we commissioned Groupe Ambition to conduct their independent certification program. Through an organizational survey of their own design, they have assessed the quality of our internal business relationships as perceived by our employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Listed on Branham300 for Second Consecutive Year</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-branham300-second-consecutive-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-branham300-second-consecutive-year/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, June 6, 2017: CloudOps has once again been listed on the Branham300, ranking at number 227 among Canada’s most-profitable public and private technology companies. The prestigious list ranks companies based on revenue and profitability. CloudOps is pleased and honoured to be part of this elite group for a second year. This reinforces CloudOps’ strategic plans in cloud platform management, telco and enterprise shared services sectors, all of which are steadily growing with the adoption of cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps and Datera Announce Apache CloudStack Integration for Web-Scale Storage Service</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-datera-apache-cloudstack-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-datera-apache-cloudstack-integration/</guid>
      <description>Software-Defined, Automated, Shared Storage Infrastructure Made Accessible to Open Source CloudStack Community
 CloudOps’ Expertise
Since 2005, CloudOps has focused on delivering vendor-agnostic cloud services with open source at its core. Companies who wish to take advantage of cloud infrastructure for various reasons including agility, elasticity, reliability, and right-sizing of infrastructure have benefitted greatly from CloudOps’ technical and business expertise in delivering cloud solutions.
Apache CloudStack (ACS) has been a major part of CloudOps’ open source IaaS offering to companies who wish to create both private and public cloud deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Ranks No. 356 on the 2016 PROFIT 500</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ranks-profit-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ranks-profit-500/</guid>
      <description>– PROFIT magazine unveils 28th annual list of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies –
Montreal, QC (September 15, 2016) Canadian Business and PROFIT today ranked CloudOps No. 356 on the 28th annual PROFIT 500, the definitive ranking of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies. Published in the October issue of Canadian Business and at PROFITguide.com, the PROFIT 500 ranks Canadian businesses by their five-year revenue growth.
CloudOps made the 2016 PROFIT 500 list with five-year revenue growth of 142%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Releases Names of Sponsors for Apache CloudStack™ Collab Conference</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/sponsorship-for-apache-cloudstack-collab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/sponsorship-for-apache-cloudstack-collab/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 27th 2016:CloudOps is excited to announce the sponsors for #ccc2016mtl. With their support, this event will successfully bring together the community in a robust gathering with multiple avenues for collaboration, discussion and creativity. This Collab is a grassroots event, bringing together this community after a year of immense change. The sponsors of the Collab have had an important role in shaping the content of the event, as well as being integral to the success of the Apache CloudStack project as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Will Stevens As The New Apache™ CloudStack Vice-President</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/will-stevens-apache-cloudstack-vice-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/will-stevens-apache-cloudstack-vice-president/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 27th 2016:CloudOps is excited to announce that Will Stevens, Lead Developer at CloudOps, has been named as the new Vice-President of the Apache CloudStack project. At the ASF meeting on May 18th, the board passed the resolution appointing Stevens to this position.
CloudOps makes this announcement with the full support and enthusiasm of the entire team and community. Stevens played a central role moving forward on the 4.9 release management duties, and is actively working to improve Apache CloudStack Github-based workflow and continuous integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Announces IDC Vendor Profile</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-announces-idc-vendor-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-announces-idc-vendor-profile/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to announce that IDC has created a vendor profile which gives a unique glimpse into a company experiencing phenomenal growth. CloudOps is poised, as the report concludes, to continue its expansion in the market over the next few years.
International Data Corporation (IDC) leads the world in providing market research and intelligence as well as advisory services to the IT market. IDC aids individuals and businesses in making “fact-based decisions” on strategic decisions and market growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of Canada’s Top ICT Companies by Branham300</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-branham300/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-branham300/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, April 20th 2016: CloudOps is named one of Canada’s top ICT companies by Branham300, ranking at 221 on this year’s list of Canada’s most-profitable companies. This recognition comes at a pivotal time for CloudOps, as it is poised for hyper growth over the next year. CloudOps is thrilled to be recognized for its growth and profitability even as it accelerates its investment in the next generation of cloud computing solutions for software companies, telecom, and enterprise shared services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Partners with Mirantis</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-partners-with-mirantis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-partners-with-mirantis/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack has dominated conversations in the cloud computing industry for some time as the open source foundation receives funding, code contributions and support from many important players in the space. More than 20 distinct OpenStack projects have been launched in the last 5 years. 
At CloudOps, we are strong supporters of open source communities, contributing to both OpenStack and Apache CloudStack projects. Our CEO, Ian Rae, often compares the two technologies to Playmobil vs Lego; basically that with Playmobil you have a kit of pre-molded parts which allow you to get to play almost right away, whereas Lego lets you customize down to the individual bricks of the infrastructure…and while Lego takes longer to build, it can also be re-configured to meet changing needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Named One of Deloitte’s Technology Fast 50TM Companies</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-named-one-of-deloittes-technology-fast-50tm-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-named-one-of-deloittes-technology-fast-50tm-companies/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, November 12, 2015 — CloudOps is named as one of Canada’s fastest growing technology companies in the 18th annual Deloitte Technology Fast&amp;nbsp;50TM&amp;nbsp;awards for demonstrating bold innovation, dedicated leadership and strong growth. CloudOps ranked 40 with 207 percent in revenue growth from 2011 to 2014. This is the second consecutive year that CloudOps has been ranked.
The Deloitte Technology Fast&amp;nbsp;50TM&amp;nbsp;program celebrates leaders in the Canadian technology industry and tracks the successful growth of Canadian-grown leaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps CEO Featured in KPMG’s The Next Million</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ceo-featured-in-kpmgs-the-next-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ceo-featured-in-kpmgs-the-next-million/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps CEO, Ian Rae, was featured in KPMG Canada’s quarterly edition of The Next Million, a magazine about Canadian entrepreneurship. The issue’s theme is cloud computing and companies that have successfully leveraged the cloud to scale their software applications, e-commerce sites, and employee mobility. 
Rae, as a leading figure in the Canadian and international cloud computing space, is being called a “cloud creator.” &amp;nbsp;He founded CloudOps ten years ago and the company has tripled in size in the last three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Ranks No. 204 on the 2015 PROFIT 500</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ranks-no-204-on-the-2015-profit-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-ranks-no-204-on-the-2015-profit-500/</guid>
      <description>– PROFIT magazine unveils 27thannual list of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies –
Montreal, QC (September 17, 2015) Canadian Businessand PROFIT today ranked CloudOps No. 204 on the 27thannual PROFIT 500, the definitive ranking of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies. Published in the October issue of Canadian Businessand at PROFITguide.com, the PROFIT 500 ranks Canadian businesses by their five-year revenue growth. 
CloudOps made the 2015 PROFIT 500 list with five-year revenue growth of 300%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Becomes the First Canadian Citrix Specialist in Networking for Data Centre</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/cloudops-becomes-the-first-canadian-citrix-specialist-in-networking-for-data-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/cloudops-becomes-the-first-canadian-citrix-specialist-in-networking-for-data-centre/</guid>
      <description>As Citrix launches its new partner specialist program, CloudOps receives prestigious designation
MONTREAL – CloudOps, a&amp;nbsp;cloud solutions provider and Citrix Gold Partner, announces its most recent Citrix certification as a Networking for Data Centre specialist. The specialization provides a framework for partners to demonstrate technical competency, end-to-end sales capability and service delivery expertise.
The new certification program was announced in early 2015 and allows for a partner to highlight their investments and expertise in a solutions category; virtualization, mobility, or networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing cloud.ca – enterprise cloud in Canada</title>
      <link>/cloudops-press/announcing-cloud-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloudops-press/announcing-cloud-ca/</guid>
      <description>We’ve spent much of the past few years helping to design and deploy both private and public clouds internationally, largely atop the Citrix CloudPlatform architecture and the most operationally mature open source technologies available from the CloudStack and OpenStack projects. With this experience under our belts, we’re taking the cover off something significant: our own secure multi-tenant cloud.
The cloud landscape has changed significantly, and now clouds are an essential tool in the IT toolbox—and Canadians deserve these tools close at hand to maintain data sovereignty and comply with privacy regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>