<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on CloudOps</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on CloudOps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create and Inspect Kubernetes Deployments</title>
      <link>/blog/how-to-create-and-inspect-kubernetes-deployments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-to-create-and-inspect-kubernetes-deployments/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to get started with Kubernetes, this blog post will teach you the basics of deployments.
What is a Kubernetes deployment? A deployment is one of the many Kubernetes objects. In technical terms, it currently encapsulates the following (which we will be covering below):
 Pod specification Replica count Deployment strategy  In practical terms, you can think of a deployment as an instance of an application with it’s associated configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways to Prepare Remote Teams for DevOps Adoption</title>
      <link>/blog/3-ways-to-prepare-remote-teams-for-devops-adoption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/3-ways-to-prepare-remote-teams-for-devops-adoption/</guid>
      <description>DevOps is a combination of cultural philosophies, practices, and tools that increase an organization’s ability to deliver applications and services at high velocity. But it cannot be achieved simply by containerizing applications and hiring a few DevOps engineers. The adoption of bleeding-edge tools is not enough on its own to deliver the benefits of DevOps. This is especially true for today’s remote workforce. There are several mistakes that are all too common for organizations trying to adopt DevOps, but chief among them is the failure to properly structure teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps’ Workshops are Eligible for the PACME Program</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-workshops-are-eligible-for-the-pacme-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-workshops-are-eligible-for-the-pacme-program/</guid>
      <description>Thursday, May 7, 2020 – CloudOps is pleased to announce participation in the Programme actions concertées pour le maintien en emploi (PACME) offered by the Government of Quebec.
The purpose of the PACME program is to support businesses that have experienced a decline in their operations as a result of the COVID-19 pandemic. It is a program of the Ministère du Travail, de l’Emploi et de la Solidarité sociale, offered in collaboration with the Commision des partenaires du marché du travail, which aims to provide direct financial support to businesses in order to promote training and the implementation of good human resources management practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Work from Home Best Practices: Curated Tips and Tricks</title>
      <link>/blog/our-work-from-home-best-practices-curated-tips-and-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/our-work-from-home-best-practices-curated-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year, I moved from leading the marketing group to HR. While I am still happily driving CloudOps’ community participation, I am now also responsible for ongoing learning for our teams. My very first training mission was to research, curate, and present best practices for working from home (including practical and wellness tips on how to optimize remote work pandemic or not) from the plethora of articles that exist on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ways to Cut Cloud Consumption Costs</title>
      <link>/blog/8-ways-to-cut-cloud-consumption-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/8-ways-to-cut-cloud-consumption-costs/</guid>
      <description>People leverage the cloud for many reasons. More often than not, the need to cut costs ranks high among them. And while the cloud does offer significant benefits that include cost-efficiency, some organizations have found out the hard way that this isn’t necessarily true as they scale. Cloud native infrastructures are complex entities that must be managed properly to scale cost-effectively. In this blog, we identify eight ways that can help your organization optimize its cloud usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing HR into the Cloud: The Remote Future of Interviewing</title>
      <link>/blog/bringing-hr-into-the-cloud-the-remote-future-of-interviewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/bringing-hr-into-the-cloud-the-remote-future-of-interviewing/</guid>
      <description>There are companies still talking about digital transformation in 2020, and you’re clearly behind the curve if you’re one of them. While the disparity between those who have gone digital and those who haven’t has been deepening for a while, it became obvious when COVID-19 forced us all to move our offices into our homes. The days of companies offering remote work as a luxury or something only to be used in extreme or rare circumstances are over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of The Financial Times The Americas’ Fastest Growing Companies in 2020</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-named-one-of-the-financial-times-the-americas-fastest-growing-companies-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-named-one-of-the-financial-times-the-americas-fastest-growing-companies-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, Quebec, April 8th 2020 — CloudOps has been recognized as part of The Financial Times inaugural list of The Americas’ Fastest Growing Companies 2020. This prestigious award is presented by The Financial Times and Statista Inc., the world-leading statistics portal and industry ranking provider.
The FT The Americas’ Fastest Growing Companies is comprised of enterprises that have contributed most heavily to economic growth. 500 companies are featured on the list, which was announced online on April 6, 2020 and can currently be viewed on this page of the FT website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anthos: Application Modernization for Hybrid and Multi-Cloud Environments</title>
      <link>/blog/anthos-application-modernization-for-hybrid-and-multi-cloud-environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/anthos-application-modernization-for-hybrid-and-multi-cloud-environments/</guid>
      <description>Anthos is an open hybrid- and multi-cloud application platform pioneered by Google. It is built on open source technologies including Kubernetes, Istio, and Knative. It is the logical extension of GKE on-prem, as it augments Google’s first entrance into the enterprise data center with a suite of open source solutions that cover areas including networking, storage, registry, logging, and monitoring. Anthos brings multiple services together to facilitate scalability, interoperability, containerization, data sovereignty, and security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Work: One Way of Supporting Employees</title>
      <link>/blog/remote-work-one-way-of-supporting-employees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/remote-work-one-way-of-supporting-employees/</guid>
      <description>From the first day I started working as the office manager at CloudOps it felt like I was working from home all the time because that’s what CloudOps became to me; my second home. I immediately became friends with everybody at work. I felt welcomed with open arms and supported. People would ask me how my first week was going. Eventually, as time passed, people began to ask me how they could support me or if they could help me with something, especially when they saw me struggling to reach the top shelves in the kitchen (I’m four feet and eleven inches tall).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps’ Commitment to Enhance Your Business Throughout COVID-19</title>
      <link>/blog/press-release-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/press-release-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>To our customers, partners, users, and friends,
As the global COVID-19 outbreak continues to evolve, we want to share the steps CloudOps is taking to help ensure the well-being of our employees and communities, as well as the continuity of our business.
We know that CloudOps has an important role in your business — whether that’s through product and service delivery or events, training, support, and consulting. Although we don’t foresee any interruptions to our core business operations, we are actively enhancing services to support an increase in customer demand for cloud services, including virtual desktops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Augmentation vs. Project-Based Services for DevOps and Cloud Projects</title>
      <link>/blog/staff-augmentation-vs-project-based-services-for-devops-and-cloud-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/staff-augmentation-vs-project-based-services-for-devops-and-cloud-projects/</guid>
      <description>DevOps tools and practices accelerate software release cycles, but their adoption can be a tricky process. The supply of skilled engineers has not always kept up with demand, there is an overwhelming array of tools to choose from, and the cultural changes required can meet resistance. You might be struggling to find clearly defined blueprints for navigating the DevOps and application platform landscapes, and you may be evaluating staff augmentation or project-based services, which include both consulting and professional services, as ways to accelerate your initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to 2020!</title>
      <link>/blog/welcome-to-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/welcome-to-2020/</guid>
      <description>“Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic.”
Arthur C. Clarke
 Most people would consider today’s technology to be magic – so sophisticated it is not apparent to most people how it works, or even that it should even be possible. Cloud computing and related technologies such as Kubernetes (well implemented) or even our own CloudMC and cloud.ca products exhibit magical qualities. Today’s technologists are modern-day witches and wizards, instead of spells, potions, and recipes we have playbooks, git repositories, and CI/CD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing, Data Pipelines, Kubernetes, and Neural Networks in Ecology</title>
      <link>/blog/remote-sensing-data-pipelines-kubernetes-and-neural-networks-in-ecology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/remote-sensing-data-pipelines-kubernetes-and-neural-networks-in-ecology/</guid>
      <description>The GitHub repo for this project can be found at: https://github.com/TristansCloud/YellowstonesVegitiation
“Remote sensing is the acquisition of information about an object or phenomenon without making physical contact with the object… [and] generally refers to the use of satellite or aircraft based sensor technologies.”
It’s the lazy persons data collection. The ‘scan the entire world every day’ data collection. Remote sensing has given us a continuous stream of data on the state of the world, revolutionizing agriculture, international defence, environmental monitoring, crisis management, telecommunications, weather forecasting, firefighting, and many other fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eastern Canada’s Kubernetes &#43; Cloud Native Meetups – Winter 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-cloud-native-meetups-winter-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-cloud-native-meetups-winter-2019/</guid>
      <description>The last series of Kubernetes + Cloud Native meetups in 2019 have come to a close. Our roadshow took us to Ottawa, Toronto, Kitchener-Waterloo, Montreal, and Quebec. Each meetup began with a recap of the KubeCon San Diego as well as news about the recent releases of Kubernetes 1.16 and 1.17, Istio 1.3 and 1.4, and Helm 3. A variety of subjects were then discussed, and we were excited to see such active participation from Eastern Canada’s communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Top 8 Blog Posts from 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/our-top-8-blog-posts-from-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/our-top-8-blog-posts-from-2019/</guid>
      <description>As 2019 comes to a close, here are our top 8 blog posts from the year. We hope they’ll give you a glimpse into the state of the information technology industry and its future.&amp;nbsp;
Comparing Service Meshes: Istio, Linkerd, and Consul Connect Service meshes have become the solution to the networking problems that containers and microservices present. Our top-performing blog post of 2019 compares Istio, Linkerd, and Consul Connect as service meshes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Now a Kubernetes Training Partner</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-now-a-kubernetes-training-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-now-a-kubernetes-training-partner/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is happy to announce membership of the newly-founded Kubernetes Training Partner (KTP) program. Run by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), the KTP program focuses on furthering the educational efforts of Kubernetes Certified Service Providers (KCSP). CloudOps provides support, consulting, professional services, as well as training for organizations seeking to embrace cloud native solutions. As Dan Kohn, Executive Director of CNCF said:
“CloudOps has demonstrated a deep knowledge of Kubernetes, as well as noteworthy community initiative around cloud native technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Listed on Branham300 for Second Consecutive Year</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-branham300-second-consecutive-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-branham300-second-consecutive-year/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, June 6, 2017: CloudOps has once again been listed on the Branham300, ranking at number 227 among Canada’s most-profitable public and private technology companies. The prestigious list ranks companies based on revenue and profitability. CloudOps is pleased and honoured to be part of this elite group for a second year. This reinforces CloudOps’ strategic plans in cloud platform management, telco and enterprise shared services sectors, all of which are steadily growing with the adoption of cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Realms – Own your Destiny in the Cloud</title>
      <link>/blog/podcast-own-your-destiny-in-the-cloud-episode-1-devops-realms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/podcast-own-your-destiny-in-the-cloud-episode-1-devops-realms/</guid>
      <description>In this first episode of ‘Own your Destiny in the Cloud,’ Marc Paré, Chief Commercial Officer at CloudOps, discussed DevOps realms with Jesse Hurkens, VP of Consulting and Transformation Services at CloudOps. They spoke about how DevOps impacts business value and how it can be found in three different realms of a technology stack.

TranscriptMP – We hear a lot today about DevOps adoption in the industry, and its value is being understood both by technical teams and business executives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Cloud Native Telcos – Own your Destiny in the Cloud</title>
      <link>/blog/the-future-of-cloud-native-telcos-own-your-destiny-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-future-of-cloud-native-telcos-own-your-destiny-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Ian Rae and Maddison Long discussed the future of the telecommunication industry. They focused on the impact of open source adoption, increased competition between cloud providers, and the ability of cloud native telcos to provide differentiated cloud and networking services in their target markets. Listen to the podcast below.

TranscriptML – What would you like a telco to take away from this conversation if you were to personify them as a person?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Mistakes To Avoid When Adopting DevOps</title>
      <link>/blog/top-10-mistakes-to-avoid-when-adopting-devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/top-10-mistakes-to-avoid-when-adopting-devops/</guid>
      <description>A CIO decides it’s time for their organization to adopt DevOps. They hire a team of digital unicorns, adopt an array of cutting-edge tools, and are disappointed when they don’t see results. All the ideas, projects, products, and teams being introduced are held back by increasingly outdated cultural norms, processes, infrastructure, and skills. Nothing is aligned with the new operational models and technologies being introduced, and the digital unicorns are locked behind a dam along with their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use a Palo Alto Networks firewall with CloudStack</title>
      <link>/blog/use-a-palo-alto-networks-firewall-with-cloudstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/use-a-palo-alto-networks-firewall-with-cloudstack/</guid>
      <description>Today we added a setup guide to the official Apache CloudStack documentation for the new features we developed to integrate the Palo Alto Networks firewall into CloudStack as a service provider.
Check out the documentation…
Start taking advantage of the Palo Alto Networks firewall orchestration in CloudStack by following the simple setup guide. Once the initial setup is done, CloudStack takes over and does all of the orchestration of the firewall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Promise Our Customers</title>
      <link>/blog/what-we-promise-our-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what-we-promise-our-customers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Own your destiny in the cloud.
At CloudOps, we believe that the successful adoption of DevOps is required to survive, even thrive, in today’s software-differentiated economy. By evolving their tools, processes, and cultures, our customers can embark on a journey towards delivering great products faster.
Our approach to DevOps is highlighted in our mission statement, to help customers own their destinies in the cloud. We empower our customers with DevOps, so they can make informed technology choices that reduce the risk of their investments and give them optionality and leverage over their suppliers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why private cloud matters</title>
      <link>/blog/why-private-cloud-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-private-cloud-matters/</guid>
      <description>by Pierre-Luc Bisaillon
I read a recent Gartner insight that predicts that the use of the word cloud will drop off in 2013, to be replaced by better descriptors of business value. Whether or not we use it less, we will continue to use it a lot.
These days when I define what I mean by cloud, I return to the NIST definition, and use the following table to illustrate the options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re Always Wrong About Your IT Needs and Here Is Why</title>
      <link>/blog/youre-always-wrong-about-your-it-needs-and-here-is-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/youre-always-wrong-about-your-it-needs-and-here-is-why/</guid>
      <description>One of the hardest things I have learned over my career in IT is that no matter how diligently you work to understand and meet business requirements, you almost always end up with too many or too few resources, too early or too late.
While the problem is often due to poor delivery of IT projects and product capabilities, even more frequently it is because either the anticipated business demand isn’t there (and you’re left with greatly under-utilized assets) or, the level of demand is hugely underestimated and the project becomes a victim of its own success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOpsDays Montreal 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/devopsdays-montreal-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/devopsdays-montreal-2019/</guid>
      <description>The second edition of DevOpsDays Montreal took place on November 5 and 6. CloudOps was excited to be at this event which brought together community members from across Eastern Canada in celebration of all things DevOps. The two days were jam-packed with talks in both English and French, open spaces, and workshops.&amp;nbsp;
The first day started with a talk by Richard Fontana called “Open Source: Everything’s fine,” an interesting look into the legalities of open source software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Success with the DevOps Health Radar</title>
      <link>/blog/assessing-success-with-the-devops-health-radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/assessing-success-with-the-devops-health-radar/</guid>
      <description>DevOps increases an organization’s ability to deliver applications and services at high velocity, evolving and improving products at a faster pace than organizations using traditional software development and infrastructure management processes. This is accomplished by redesigning processes so development and operations tasks are no longer fully separated by silos.
At CloudOps, we help customers design, build, and operate cloud platforms with DevOps tools and practices. The first phase is always to provide a DevOps Platform and Practices Assessment (DPPA), which provides an objective understanding of the business impact, technical risks, and path to DevOps best practices and cloud native development and delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Best-of-Breed Toolbox for Using Cloud</title>
      <link>/blog/a-best-of-breed-toolbox-for-using-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/a-best-of-breed-toolbox-for-using-cloud/</guid>
      <description>The number of tools in the cloud native landscape has exploded in the past few years, and it can be difficult to know which tool is right for which job. Cloud native technology stacks are comprised of several layers, each of which requires in-depth knowledge to optimize.
We’re cloud and tool agnostic but opinionated and know that we serve our customers best with a mix of open source and proprietary tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eastern Canada’s Kubernetes and Cloud Native Meetups – Summer 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-meetups-summer-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-meetups-summer-2019/</guid>
      <description>Summer was punctuated with many great talks and cupcakes as we closed off the season with the Kubernetes Birthday Bash. Our roadshow took us to Quebec City, Montreal, Ottawa, Toronto and Kitchener-Waterloo, where our CNCF Ambassador, Ayrat Khayretdinov, relayed important news and updates from the CNCF. Most notable is KubeCon North America taking place on November 18th to 21st in San Diego. Thefull list of speakers has just been released and we are happy to announce that some of our own meetup members are included in that list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Need to Know About BizDevOps</title>
      <link>/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-about-bizdevops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/everything-you-need-to-know-about-bizdevops/</guid>
      <description>It’s proven that DevOps increases the ability of an organization to deliver services at high velocity.&amp;nbsp;
But what if the same tools and practices that accelerate feature delivery can also be used to generate greater business value?
That’s where BizDevOps comes in.
BizDevOps integrates feedback from the business side of an organization into its delivery cycles, effectively ensuring features released through DevOps cycles are built specifically to serve business objectives. A streamlined workflow is created from business strategy to deployment, allowing DevOps metrics to become aligned with high-level business KPIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of Canada’s Top Growing Companies.</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-growing-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-growing-companies/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to announce it placed No. 294 on the inaugural Report on Business ranking of Canada’s Top Growing Companies.
Launched in 2019, the Canada’s Top Growing Companies ranking program aims to celebrate entrepreneurial achievement in Canada by identifying and amplifying the success of growth-minded, independent businesses in Canada.&amp;nbsp;
Canada’s Top Growing Companies ranks Canadian companies on three-year revenue growth. CloudOps earned its spot with three-year growth of 96%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Books to Become Better at DevOps</title>
      <link>/blog/9-books-to-become-better-at-devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/9-books-to-become-better-at-devops/</guid>
      <description>Interested in learning more about DevOps but don’t know where to start? We’ve got you covered.
We asked some people on our team for their favourite books on DevOps. Here are a few that explain how DevOps can truly transform the way technology serves your business.
 Lean Enterprise: How High-Performance Organizations Innovate at Scale This is a practical guide to Lean and Agile principles, both of which are at the foundation of DevOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolving towards a Cloud Centre of Excellence in AWS</title>
      <link>/blog/evolving-towards-a-cloud-centre-of-excellence-in-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/evolving-towards-a-cloud-centre-of-excellence-in-aws/</guid>
      <description>AWS came out with its first public cloud offering in 2006, bringing with it extensive debate on the benefits of cloud migration. Claims that migrating to the cloud would cut costs and provide the ability to efficiently respond to demand fluctuations led to many organizations migrating into the cloud, most lifting and shifting their legacy infrastructures into AWS.
AWS has since continued growing its offering and currently boasts the highest market share and richest library of features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Cloud Native: How to Migrate your Applications into the Cloud</title>
      <link>/blog/become-cloud-native-how-to-migrate-your-applications-into-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/become-cloud-native-how-to-migrate-your-applications-into-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Carefully thinking about what kind of cloud platform will suit your business and technical requirements will let you own your destiny in the cloud. To learn more about how you can analyze your technology stack, read our white paper, ‘A Checklist for your Cloud Migration Strategy.’
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiz: Are you a Kubernetes Unicorn?</title>
      <link>/blog/quiz-are-you-a-kubernetes-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/quiz-are-you-a-kubernetes-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographic: Your Guide to Kubernetes Distributions</title>
      <link>/blog/infographic-your-guide-to-kubernetes-distributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/infographic-your-guide-to-kubernetes-distributions/</guid>
      <description>Our DevOps workshops will set you on the path to application to modernization. Sign your technical teams up for one of our three-day, hands-on Docker and Kubernetes workshops to learn the basis of microservices and containers.
Check out our blog post on Kubernetes vanilla tools, distributions, and managed services for a more in-depth overview.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Promise Our Customers</title>
      <link>/blog/life-at-cloudops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/life-at-cloudops/</guid>
      <description>At CloudOps, we are always looking for excellent candidates to join our tight-knit team of experts as we work and play with the latest and greatest technologies. Our culture is a shared repository of technical knowledge with which we navigate the increasingly complex cloud native landscape. We sat down with a few of our team members to ask them why they love coming into work every day. Here’s what they said about life at CloudOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of Canada’s Top ICT Companies in 2019 by Branham300</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-ict-companies-in-2019-by-branham300/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-named-one-of-canadas-top-ict-companies-in-2019-by-branham300/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to have placed 191st in the Branham300 list of Top 250 Canadian ICT companies in 2019. This is the fourth consecutive year that CloudOps has been listed in this ranking. CloudOps was listed 197th in the 2018 Branham300 ranking.
The Branham300 ranking is based on revenue and consists of Canada’s most profitable, public and private technology companies. All Top 250 companies demonstrate significant revenue growth and altogether represent over half of the nation’s ICT (Information and Communications Technology) sector revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Cloud Security with DevSecOps</title>
      <link>/blog/rethinking-cloud-security-with-devsecops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/rethinking-cloud-security-with-devsecops/</guid>
      <description>DevOps is the combination of cultural philosophies, practices, and tools that increase an organization’s ability to deliver applications and services at high velocity. By removing traditional separations between development and operations, it creates dynamic pipelines of continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) that release software in faster cycles and smaller batches. DevOps helps modernize legacy technology systems, allowing organizations to better compete in today’s data-driven software economy.
The adoption of DevOps tools and practices has exploded as a result, and the percentage of IT professionals working in DevOps teams increased from 16% in 2014 to 27% in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telcos, It’s Time to Deliver Hybrid Cloud</title>
      <link>/blog/telcos-its-time-to-deliver-hybrid-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/telcos-its-time-to-deliver-hybrid-cloud/</guid>
      <description>“Everyone wants hybrid multi-cloud” – This is what we heard from both the head of open source strategy for Google Cloud Platform and a principal program manager (in the office of the CTO) for Microsoft Azure, at the Linux Foundation’s Open Source Leadership Summit, as the overwhelmingly clear message they’re hearing from their many customers. That is to say, end users want to leverage multiple hyperscale public clouds, and regional edge computing resources, while continuing to leverage their on-prem infrastructure within their IT environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CloudOps Delivery Model – Accelerated Value Delivery through Code and Collaboration</title>
      <link>/blog/the-cloudops-delivery-model-accelerated-value-delivery-through-code-and-collaboration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-cloudops-delivery-model-accelerated-value-delivery-through-code-and-collaboration/</guid>
      <description>DevOps aligns cultural change with the speed and flexibility of cloud, containers, and modernized architectures. Successfully implemented, its combination of practices and tools will increase the delivery of applications and services at high velocity. DevOps allows organizations to pivot when needed and respond to market changes as part of finding digital solutions to their industry’s problems.
While a necessary part of digital transformation, organizations may find the process of adopting DevOps to be long, difficult, and unclear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Rook and Ceph Survival Guide</title>
      <link>/blog/the-ultimate-rook-and-ceph-survival-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-ultimate-rook-and-ceph-survival-guide/</guid>
      <description>Containers are built with statelessness as a core principle, but data must still be stored and made accessible to some services. You therefore need a solution that preserves data in the event of container restarts.
Persistent Volume Claims (PVCs) are the recommended solution to manage stateful applications in Kubernetes. With a PVC, a Pod can request and connect to volumes, which exist independent of the enclosing Pod’s lifecycle.
PVCs offer the advantage of separating Ops from Devs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is an AWS Advanced Consulting Member</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-an-aws-advanced-consulting-membe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-an-aws-advanced-consulting-membe/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to become an Advanced member of the AWS Partner Network (APN). As a consulting partner of AWS, CloudOps helps companies build or expand their businesses in AWS’ public cloud offering.
As the most mature cloud offering, AWS offers users a vast array of rich features from which to take full advantage of what the cloud has to offer. CloudOps’ membership speaks to the in-depth knowledge that our teams have with regards to AWS as well as our commitment to helping organizations transform digitally, building their businesses in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is in the Top 100 Cloud Solution Providers in Canada</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-in-the-top-100-cloud-solution-providers-in-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-in-the-top-100-cloud-solution-providers-in-canada/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to join the Top 100 (cloud) Solution Providers in Canada for Channel Daily News (CDN), owned by IT World Canada. CloudOps has been listed as the 91st solution provider in Canada and was one of eight newcomers to the list.
This ranking comes from data collected by CDN from IT solution providers across Canada. It produces an industry benchmark report that sheds light on industry trends. The results were announced at the Top 100 Solution Providers Gala last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiz: How Secure are your Containers in Azure?</title>
      <link>/blog/quiz-how-secure-are-your-containers-in-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/quiz-how-secure-are-your-containers-in-azure/</guid>
      <description> powered by
Read our ebook Azure Kubernetes Services: Container Security for a Cloud Native World to learn more about the biggest container security risks faced by enterprises as well as how to optimize solutions with AKS.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Microsoft DevOps Competency Partner</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-a-microsoft-devops-competency-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-a-microsoft-devops-competency-partner/</guid>
      <description>The Microsoft Competency Program gives partners the opportunity to demonstrate proven expertise in delivering quality solutions to specialized areas of business. Partners reach competency in given areas through a skills assessment, in which they pass exams to demonstrate product knowledge, or through proving an ability to meet performance goals.
Today, CloudOps announces its completion of the Microsoft DevOps Competency. As a DevOps partner, CloudOps has proven its expertise in helping organizations modernize their application development approaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Stevens is a Member of the Apache Software Foundation</title>
      <link>/blog/will-stevens-is-a-member-of-the-apache-software-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/will-stevens-is-a-member-of-the-apache-software-foundation/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps’ Chief Technology Officer, Will Stevens, has recently become a member of the Apache Software Foundation (ASF). He will continue encouraging the open source community and contributing to ASF projects.
The ASF is a charitable organization devoted to supporting open source software projects by nurturing communities, encouraging the development of quality code, and generating awareness of its member projects. The ASF was established in 1999 and is funded by donations and managed by volunteers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Adventure in Multi-Cloud Networking with Kubernetes and Tungsten Fabric</title>
      <link>/blog/an-adventure-in-multi-cloud-networking-with-kubernetes-and-tungsten-fabric/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/an-adventure-in-multi-cloud-networking-with-kubernetes-and-tungsten-fabric/</guid>
      <description>With a couple weeks before KubeCon and an impending presentation, I embarked on a small adventure to try networking together two different Kubernetes clusters with Tungsten Fabric, the goal being to do a live demo at the Tungsten Fabric Developers Summit.
The demo was designed to be a simplified illustration of the broader hybrid/multi-cloud use case of connecting two distinct networks in the context of Kubernetes. This use case is especially interesting in the context of migrating a set of services to Kubernetes, while still maintaining connectivity to other services in the legacy network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Service Meshes: Istio, Linkerd and Consul Connect</title>
      <link>/blog/comparing-service-meshes-istio-linkerd-and-consul-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/comparing-service-meshes-istio-linkerd-and-consul-connect/</guid>
      <description>The use of microservice-based architectures has skyrocketed in the past few years, highlighting their ability to make applications more scalable, portable, and resilient than their monolithic predecessors. But the volatile and ephemeral environments that microservices encourage can make networking inherently problematic.
It can be difficult to establish trust between microservices, slowing down operations. Canary deployments, the idea of rolling out releases to a subset of users or servers, can be complicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native Gaming: What Google Stadia has to offer</title>
      <link>/blog/cloud-native-gaming-what-google-stadia-has-to-offer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloud-native-gaming-what-google-stadia-has-to-offer/</guid>
      <description>Gamers and developers alike are finally getting a glimpse of the not-too-distant future of cloud gaming It didn’t seem that long ago that we were touting our undying allegiance to a particular console. “I am a Nintendo kid, get N or get out,” I remember some of my friends exclaiming, “Nintendo is for kids,” Xbox and Playstation devouts would say. And then, of course, there were those of us whose devotion to hardware meant that we meticulously scoured online benchmark tests in the quest to build the perfect gaming PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Russia with Love: Deploying Kubernetes in Foreign Locations</title>
      <link>/blog/to-russia-with-love-deploying-kubernetes-in-foreign-locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/to-russia-with-love-deploying-kubernetes-in-foreign-locations/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago, CloudOps started working with a large European client who wanted to migrate their workloads into Google Cloud Platform (GCP). They were looking to modernize their application with containers and use the most mature Kubernetes distribution at the time: Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE). They additionally wanted their application platform to use libraries of automation recipes based on Terraform and Ansible. CloudOps helped them through this migration process, and the architecture was completed in March, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maddison Long accepted into Forbes Technology Council</title>
      <link>/blog/maddison-long-accepted-into-forbes-technology-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/maddison-long-accepted-into-forbes-technology-council/</guid>
      <description>Maddison Long, Vice President of Products at CloudOps, a leading Canadian cloud consulting and services company focused on open source, cloud platforms, networking and DevOps, has been accepted into Forbes Technology Council, an invitation-only community for world-class CIOs, CTOs, and technology executives.
Maddison Long was vetted and selected by a review committee based on the depth and diversity of his experience. Criteria for acceptance include a track record of successfully impacting business growth metrics, as well as personal and professional achievements and honors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving Feature Velocity through Cultural Change: Why DevOps puts Mindset before Technology</title>
      <link>/blog/driving-feature-velocity-through-cultural-change-why-devops-puts-mindset-before-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/driving-feature-velocity-through-cultural-change-why-devops-puts-mindset-before-technology/</guid>
      <description>DevOps accelerates the delivery of stable, high-quality software from concept to customer by creating dynamic pipelines of continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD). A combination of cultural philosophies, practices, and tools, DevOps can increase an organization’s ability to deliver applications and services at high velocity. It can modernize operations and legacy technology infrastructures that limit the ability of many companies to compete in today’s data-driven software economy.
Culture is at the heart of digital transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Guide to Securing Containers at Scale</title>
      <link>/blog/a-brief-guide-to-securing-containers-at-scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/a-brief-guide-to-securing-containers-at-scale/</guid>
      <description>Containers have changed the way we run applications, providing means to greatly increase their speed, scalability, and efficiency. They are a form of operating system virtualization that is combined with application software packaging to create portable, reusable, and automatable ways of packaging and running applications. Ever since Kubernetes, the container orchestration system, was open sourced in 2015, the landscape of cloud native technologies has exploded alongside wide-ranging commercial adoption.
But container technologies have developed at such a fast pace that their security has often not had time to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Joined CloudOps</title>
      <link>/blog/why-i-joined-cloudops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-i-joined-cloudops/</guid>
      <description>After spending the last three years scaling up an open source network solutions startup from ground up to acquisition, I am fortunate to be starting a tremendous new opportunity with a rare sense of completion.
So, why did I decide to join my friends at CloudOps?
The short answer is simple – for the people, community and technology.
People People are the most significant challenge and opportunity when it comes to successful technology adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCF Ambassador Spill: Takeaways from KubeCon &#43; CloudNativeCon</title>
      <link>/blog/cncf-ambassador-spill-takeaways-from-kubecon-cloudnativecon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cncf-ambassador-spill-takeaways-from-kubecon-cloudnativecon/</guid>
      <description>Over 8,000 people attended KubeCon + CloudNativeCon in Seattle last month. They were there to celebrate the exponential growth of Kubernetes, the open source software for orchestrating containers. Since the first KubeCon in 2015, the cloud native community has mushroomed in size and success. As Janet Kuo stated in her keynote address, “Kubernetes is now very, very boring” – it has become an exceptionally stable platform that has reached mass commercial adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hashicorp User Group Meetup #2</title>
      <link>/blog/hashicorp-user-group-meetup-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hashicorp-user-group-meetup-2/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps was pleased to collaborate with Hashicorp User Group, fondly known as HUG, for its second DevOps Montreal meetup last night. Hosted at espace cloud.ca, the event began with beer, pizza, and mingling, before moving onto more substantive talks.
cloud.ca’s very own Clément Contini began by speaking about leveraging Hashicorp’s Terraform to create Kubernetes clusters on public clouds using the kubeadm toolkit. Additionally, he showed how to balance Terraform with the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you Need a DevOps Transformation to Survive</title>
      <link>/blog/why-you-need-a-devops-transformation-to-survive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-you-need-a-devops-transformation-to-survive/</guid>
      <description>Software is eating the world and organizations are continuously moving towards software-based solutions to their industry’s problems. They are doing so as part of digital transformations that allow them to deliver stronger financial performances.
Cloud is the enabler of this process as it is breaking down non-digital systems and clearing the way for digitally advanced processes and tools to sustain continuous, as-a-service delivery.
Organizations that improve their ability to deliver software are more able to quickly release features, pivot when needed, comply with regulations, and respond to feedback so as to attract new customers and delight existing ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native Meetups: K8s 1.13 and AKS</title>
      <link>/blog/cloud-native-meetups-k8s-1-13-and-aks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloud-native-meetups-k8s-1-13-and-aks/</guid>
      <description>This year’s final set of Kubernetes and Cloud Native meetups just took place. They kicked off in Kitchener-Waterloo on November 29th, and continued in Montreal December 3rd, Ottawa December 4th, Toronto December 5th, and Quebec December 6th. In preparation for the upcoming KubeCon and CloudNativeCon in Seattle, a wide range of open source solutions were discussed and, as always, beer and pizza provided.
The meetups in Montreal, Ottawa, Toronto, and Quebec began with an update of the CNCF landscape by Ayrat Khayretdinov, CNCF Ambassador and Cloud Solutions Architect at CloudOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eastern Canada’s Kubernetes and Cloud Native Meetups – Winter Edition</title>
      <link>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-meetups-winter-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-meetups-winter-edition/</guid>
      <description>This year’s first set of Kubernetes and Cloud Native Meetups in Eastern Canada just took place from February 25th to March 6th, happening in Quebec City, Ottawa, Montreal, Kitchener-Waterloo, and Toronto. A wide array of topics were discussed, and CloudOps was excited to see such active participation from Eastern Canada’s cloud native communities.
Each meetup began with an update by Ayrat Khayretdinov, CNCF (Cloud Native Computing Foundation) Ambassador and Solutions Architect at CloudOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Cloud Native: Cloud Agnostic Platforms and Automation Driving Business Value</title>
      <link>/blog/why-cloud-native-cloud-agnostic-platforms-and-automation-driving-business-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-cloud-native-cloud-agnostic-platforms-and-automation-driving-business-value/</guid>
      <description>As the benefits of the cloud become increasingly evident, more and more organizations are migrating their workloads. Yet taking full advantage of what the cloud has to offer can require altering your application to make it cloud native.
What is Cloud Native: ‘Cloud native’ describes any application that was built to live in the cloud and designed to optimize its potential. It applies to applications that have successfully leveraged the operational model of the cloud with containers and harness business value while remaining cloud agnostic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginner’s Guide to the CNCF Landscape</title>
      <link>/blog/the-beginners-guide-to-the-cncf-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-beginners-guide-to-the-cncf-landscape/</guid>
      <description>The cloud native ecosystem can be complicated and confusing. Its myriad of open source projects are supported by the constant contributions of a vibrant and expansive community. The Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) has a landscape mapthat shows the full extent of cloud native solutions, many of which are under their umbrella.
As a CNCF ambassador, I am actively engaged in promoting community efforts and cloud native education throughout Canada. At CloudOps I lead workshops on Docker and Kubernetes that provide an introduction to cloud native technologies and help DevOps teams operate their applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOpsDays Montreal</title>
      <link>/blog/devopsdays-montreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/devopsdays-montreal/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps was pleased to sponsor DevOpsDays Montreal, which took place on October 10th and 11th. Featuring a wide range of speakers and activities, the event brought together DevOps practitioners throughout Montreal.
The event kicked off in the morning with a keynote by Alistair Croll entitled ‘Innovation, Disruption, and Discontinuity: Technology isn’t Interesting.’ Innovation has traditionally continued or disrupted markets, but adaptivity is becoming increasingly necessary as we move away from economies of scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Takeaways from Liz Rice: Pop-Up Meetup on Container Security</title>
      <link>/blog/takeaways-from-liz-rice-pop-up-meetup-on-container-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/takeaways-from-liz-rice-pop-up-meetup-on-container-security/</guid>
      <description>Last night’s pop-up meetup featured Liz Rice, a renowned expert in container security and technical evangelist at Aqua Security. As an active participant of the CNCF and as co-chair of KubeCon and CloudNativeCon, Liz was able to share her extensive experience with cloud native technologies. The event took place on October 4th at Complexe Desjardins. View&amp;nbsp;Liz’s slide deck here.
The evening began with a fireside chat where Robert Masse, Partner and Risk Advisor at Deloitte, and Marc Pare, CCO at CloudOps, interviewed Liz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Talks Open Source at ApacheCon 2018</title>
      <link>/blog/open-source-apachecon-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/open-source-apachecon-2018/</guid>
      <description>ApacheCon North Americawas held in Montreal this year from September&amp;nbsp;24thto 27th. The event featured a CloudStack Collab Conference, in which containers, DevOps, IoT, servers, and web frameworks amongst many other subjects were covered. CloudOps was pleased to sponsor the event, and even more so to participate.
Syed Ahmed discussed&amp;nbsp;A Journey to CloudStack&amp;nbsp;with Francois Nadeau from Ticketmaster, who partnered with CloudOps for help leveraging Infrastructure-as-a-Service. Our sisters company, cloud.ca, made a few presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does the Service Mesh spell the end for Middleware?</title>
      <link>/blog/does-the-service-mesh-spell-the-end-for-middleware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/does-the-service-mesh-spell-the-end-for-middleware/</guid>
      <description>Middleware is perhaps fading away in the place of the service mesh as Istio and related technologies continue to garner momentum. They both oversee communication between various applications and services, but can differ substantially in operations as well as paradigms. Prominent in service-oriented architectures, could middleware become irrelevant in today’s container-focused world?
Middleware
Often called “software glue”, middlewarebrings an application and its underlying databases together. It connects a client’s network-generated requests to back-end data, enabling communication by concentrating all messaging in one pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast: Cloud, Innovation, and Updates from Google Next 2018</title>
      <link>/blog/podcast-cloud-innovation-and-updates-from-google-next-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/podcast-cloud-innovation-and-updates-from-google-next-2018/</guid>
      <description>Ian Rae, CloudOps’ CEO and founder,&amp;nbsp;discussed&amp;nbsp;cloud innovation with&amp;nbsp;Rob Hirschfeld on the most recent episode of ‘L8ist Sh9y Podcast’.

Recorded while Ian was at Google Next 2018, this episode explored how the cloud industry has not always evolved as predicted. It wasn’t believed early on that Google would emerge as a big player and cloud resources were expected to become commodities. Instead, we have seen the emergence of highly differentiated cloud platforms, and Google has staked a position as the ‘Engineer’s Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Containerization of Machine Learning: TensorFlow, Kubernetes and Kubeflow</title>
      <link>/blog/machine-learning-tensorflow-kubernetes-and-kubeflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/machine-learning-tensorflow-kubernetes-and-kubeflow/</guid>
      <description>Machine learning (ML) is a method of data analysis for identifying patterns and predicting future probabilities. It is part of research on artificial intelligence (AI). By inputting data with predetermined answers into mathematical models, computers can train themselves to predict future unknown sets of inputs.
While ML has so far been successful in solving specified tasks, the analysis of data with more complex parameters requires models that can be deployed at scale with simplified operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a Cloud Provider as part of your Migration Strategy</title>
      <link>/blog/how-to-choose-a-cloud-provider-6-factors-to-think-about-when-migrating-to-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-to-choose-a-cloud-provider-6-factors-to-think-about-when-migrating-to-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Ever since AWS came out with its first public cloud offering in 2006, the industry has grown to an estimated $178 billionof revenues per year. Cloud computing has enabled highly dynamic and scalable infrastructures that can deliver significant returns on investment. The migration of workloads from on-premise facilities to cloud offerings is often cited as a business priority. Nonetheless, less than half of all companies had placed any workloads in public clouds by the beginning of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Infrastructure as Code with GCP Deployment Manager: Your third step towards DevOps automation</title>
      <link>/blog/creating-infrastructure-as-code-with-gcp-deployment-manager-your-third-step-towards-devops-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creating-infrastructure-as-code-with-gcp-deployment-manager-your-third-step-towards-devops-automation/</guid>
      <description>Geeking out at Google Next 18this week in California, I grabbed a Chromebook from the Grab-and-Go team (awesome initiative) and decided to finish this Infrastructure as Code trilogy.
In the previous two posts we focused on Infrastructure as Code, viewing Terraform as our multi-cloud capable swiss army knife.&amp;nbsp;But what if you just want to leverage a specific cloud infrastructure deployment service?
Google Cloud Platform (GCP) has such a tool and it’s called Deployment Manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rancher 2.0: Exciting Features You Should Know About</title>
      <link>/blog/rancher-2-0-exciting-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/rancher-2-0-exciting-features/</guid>
      <description>Rancher 2.0 was made GA (generally available) on May 1st, and there is quite a bit to be excited about. Providing a managed Kubernetes distribution, Rancher is deterministic in deployment and lightweight in installation. Its simplicity and flexibility can make it ideal for straightforward infrastructures that lack managed Kubernetes offerings and need to be built from the ground up. While previous versions already made for a fairly useable platform, Rancher 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native Meetups: K8s 1.11, Helm, PostgreSQL, and Traefik</title>
      <link>/blog/cloud-native-meetups-k8s-1-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloud-native-meetups-k8s-1-11/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes celebrated its fourth birthday across eastern Canada this week with a series of cloud native meetups in Montreal, Quebec City, Ottawa, Toronto, and Kitchener-Waterloo. This quarter’s series of Kubernetes and Cloud Native meetups brought together a range of speakers, including Ayrat Khayretdinov, Baruch Sadogursky, Jonathan Katz, and Daniel Tomcej. Below is an overview of the content of their presentations.
A Kubernetes 1.11 update reviewing the ecosystem by our very own CNCF ambassador, Ayrat Khayretdninov, kicked off each meetup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Red Hat Application Platform Partner</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-red-hat-application-platform-partner-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-red-hat-application-platform-partner-initiative/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to become a member of the Red Hat Application Platform Partner Initiative (APP). Consisting of partners focused on application platforms with emerging technologies, the APP Initiative encourages deeper collaboration between Red Hat and its partners in helping organizations modernise their application platforms.
Red Hat OpenShift unites developers and IT operations on a single Kubernetes platform to build, deploy, and manage containerized applications in any public, private, or hybrid cloud environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps listed in the Branham300 in 2018</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-listed-in-the-branham300-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-listed-in-the-branham300-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to be listed in the Branham300 Top 250 companies in 2018&amp;nbsp;for the third consecutive year. CloudOps has been listed as the 197th company, up from last year. Consisting of Canada’s most profitable, public and private technology companies, the ranking is based on revenue. All Top 250 companies have demonstrated significant revenue growth in every year since 2009, and altogether they represent over half of the nation’s ICT (Information and Communications Technology) sector revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montreal Cloud Native Day 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/montreal-cloud-native-day-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/montreal-cloud-native-day-2019/</guid>
      <description>Montreal’s first Cloud Native Day was last Tuesday. The event brought together Kubernetes and cloud native communities from across Eastern Canada and featured a full day of talks. The event was attended by over 200 cloud native enthusiasts and culminated the Kubernetes and cloud native meetups run by CloudOps in Montreal, Toronto, Ottawa, Kitchener-Waterloo, and Quebec City.
Luc Perkins from the CNCF and Vicky Brasseur from Juniper Networks began the day with a keynote called ‘A well-grounded Cloud: Exploring the foundations of cloud native.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Chose Ansible for Automating Configuration Management</title>
      <link>/blog/why-we-chose-ansible-for-automating-configuration-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-we-chose-ansible-for-automating-configuration-management/</guid>
      <description>Ansible is an open source tool for automating configuration management, deployment, and orchestration. It has an agentless approach that is designed to simplify the process of deploying VMs while allowing greater control over and agility in their configuration. While Ansible can be used to deploy and maintain standardized server configurations via templates (Ansible Playbooks), it can also be modified to apply custom configurations for individual machines to meet specific requirements. It is receptive to active configuration changes and uses standard SSH connectivity to execute automation workflows, reducing the management overhead and facilitating the integration of instances into a wide array of environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eastern Canada’s Kubernetes and Cloud Native Meetups – Spring Edition 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-meetups-spring-edition-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/eastern-canadas-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-meetups-spring-edition-2019/</guid>
      <description>With summer right around the corner, CloudOps held a series of Kubernetes and Cloud Native meetups in Montreal, Kitchener-Waterloo, Ottawa, Toronto, and Quebec City. In the wake of KubeCon in Barcelona, updates on the Kubernetes and cloud native ecosystem were given by Ayrat Khayretdinov, our very own CNCF ambassador.
The meetups begin in Montreal at Ubisoft’s office. Jean-Philippe Belanger from Upgrade started the meetup in Montreal with a highly anticipated talk discussing GitOps and ArgoCD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does GDPR mean for your Cloud Application?</title>
      <link>/blog/what-does-gdpr-mean-for-your-cloud-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what-does-gdpr-mean-for-your-cloud-application/</guid>
      <description>GDPR came into effect on May 25th. What first seemed like something that could be swept under the rug is quickly becoming reality as everyone scrambles to understand the extent of its implications. Even with it already here, less than 10% of businesses say they are GDPR ready. But with fines for non-compliance slated to reach €20m or 4% of total worldwide revenue from last year (whichever turns out to be more), it is clear that GDPR compliance is an imperative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A DevOps Sundae: Is SRE the Cherry on Top?</title>
      <link>/blog/devops-sundae-with-sre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/devops-sundae-with-sre/</guid>
      <description>Google first introduced Site Reliability Engineering, or SRE, to the world in 2003. Today, they have over 1,500 site reliability engineers supporting their large-scale systems amidst a continuous development and release cycle of features. The practice of site reliability engineering seeks to extend the traditional DevOps model, moving operational responsibilities into the hands of software developers. SREs build the platform that will be used by developers and operated by operators, and they require an in-depth knowledge of the DevOps and cloud native landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Kubernetes Ingresses aren’t as Difficult as You Think</title>
      <link>/blog/why-kubernetes-ingresses-arent-as-difficult-as-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-kubernetes-ingresses-arent-as-difficult-as-you-think/</guid>
      <description>How to use Ingresses to Route your Services on a Vanilla K8s DeploymentIf you’re using Kubernetes, you probably have deployments or stateful sets managing a number of pods that are running different microservices within a greater application. What use is this if your microservices can’t communicate with each other? They are running as a number of pods scheduled by Kubernetes, and these pods have assigned IPs and kubedns names that are both too mutable to be dependable for networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native Meetup: K8s 1.10 Update, K8s Image Admittance, Rancher 2.0 Cluster Management, KubeVirt, Stateful Sets, Rook &amp; Jaeger</title>
      <link>/blog/q2-cloud-native-meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/q2-cloud-native-meetups/</guid>
      <description>In the wake of the recent KubeCon, we held an exciting series of Q2 cloud native meetups in Montreal, Kitchener-Waterloo, Ottawa, Toronto, and Quebec City. Featuring a range of topics, we enjoyed discussing all things cloud native with the community.
Each meetup started with a 1.10 update of KubeCon by our very own Mike Wojcikiewicz and our CNCF ambassador, Ayrat Kharetdninov. Their update covered the most relevant keynotes, CNCF projects to overview, and some of our recent activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Compliance Confusion: Why You Need a SOC 2 Foundation</title>
      <link>/blog/overcoming-compliance-confusion-why-you-need-a-soc-2-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/overcoming-compliance-confusion-why-you-need-a-soc-2-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it’s overwhelming.
There is a rising wave of formal compliance efforts today, driven by customer demands, regulatory requirements, and/or the organizations’ desires to demonstrate its internal security controls and practices to external parties. Recent data protection laws have enshrined the individual’s right to privacy and security of their personal data across the globe. As personal information only becomes more valuable, the frequency and severity of security breaches accelerates. Organizations that fail to adequately secure their data face potentially devastating fines and loss of reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of OpenShift for the Enterprise Software Transformation</title>
      <link>/blog/the-value-of-openshift-for-the-enterprise-software-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-value-of-openshift-for-the-enterprise-software-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Red Hat OpenShift offers a full platform solution based on open source technologies. It provides DevOps teams with integrated environments that oversee key aspects of the software development life cycle. It leverages a Kubernetes platform that manages the building and deployment of Docker containers at scale, and offers rich features of its own. OpenShift can be easily integrated into pre-existing infrastructures and deployed over a multitude of cloud platforms. OpenShift is a Platform-as-a-Service that enables consistent and easy container orchestration, and reduces the effort of deploying a Kubernetes platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Generate and Use Dynamic Secrets for AWS IAM with Vault using Kubernetes &amp; Helm</title>
      <link>/blog/how-to-deploy-a-development-vault-server-to-kubernetes-using-helm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-to-deploy-a-development-vault-server-to-kubernetes-using-helm/</guid>
      <description>Your first step to securely store, access, and deploy sensitive application information In today’s API and Cloud-platform driven world, we operators, developers, and architects are presented with the critical challenge of managing application secrets, encryption, and access to any application and infrastructure in the Cloud. Securing and rotating secrets regularly and properly, both in the Cloud and on-premise, can pose a significant challenge. However, it’s essential as your DevOps team embraces Infrastructure as Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java’s Got a New Release Train: Are you on it or under it?</title>
      <link>/blog/javas-got-a-new-release-train-are-you-on-it-or-under-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/javas-got-a-new-release-train-are-you-on-it-or-under-it/</guid>
      <description>Oracle is taking a more contemporary approach to releasing new versions of the Java platform with the recent release of Java 10. Rather than letting feature readiness drive the timing of new releases, Oracle will employ a train release model. New versions will be released every six months – regardless of content. Sun Microsystems, and now Oracle, have traditionally released new versions every two to four years. With this new release train model, the Java platform will upgrade four to six times more often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Infrastructure as Code with Packer and Terraform on GCP: Your second step towards DevOps automation</title>
      <link>/blog/creating-infrastructure-as-code-with-packer-and-terraform-on-gcp-your-second-step-towards-devops-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creating-infrastructure-as-code-with-packer-and-terraform-on-gcp-your-second-step-towards-devops-automation/</guid>
      <description>Everyone wants to adopt Infrastructure as Code to configure and automate the infrastructure of their application as it embraces DevOps best practices. Figuring out ways to automate your CI/CD pipeline is at the heart of this transition, and is a huge interest of mine.
What we did last time
My last blog post was called ‘How to Deploy Consul in GCP using Terraform: Your first step towards DevOps automation.’
In my last post, I showed you how to create a fully automate the process for spinning an instance in GCP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Member of the Linux Foundation, the LFN, and the CNCF</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-linux-foundation-the-lfn-and-the-cncf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-a-member-of-the-linux-foundation-the-lfn-and-the-cncf/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps has always believed that open source software plays an important role in any cloud-based solution. By leveraging the power of community, open source projects transcend the incumbent industry players to act as a catalyst for transformation. The Linux Foundation and its subsidiary foundations provide sustainable ecosystems for these communities to grow and flourish. As a member of The Linux Foundation, the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), and The LFNetworking Fund (LFN), CloudOps is proud of its commitment to open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solving Complexity at the Network Layer with Istio</title>
      <link>/blog/mesh-your-services-with-istio-solving-complexity-at-the-network-layer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/mesh-your-services-with-istio-solving-complexity-at-the-network-layer/</guid>
      <description>Istio and the service mesh 
Developed in collaboration between Google and IBM, Istio is an open source technology that provides operational control over and behavioural insight into the service mesh of an application as a whole. Sitting above the application layer, service meshes consist of a dedicated network layer abstracted away from microservices themselves. Monitoring the service mesh, Istio enables platform-independent communication between microservices that doesn’t require changes in service code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Infrastructure as Code with Terraform in GCP: Your first step towards DevOps automation</title>
      <link>/blog/how-to-deploy-consul-in-gcp-using-terraform-your-first-step-towards-devops-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-to-deploy-consul-in-gcp-using-terraform-your-first-step-towards-devops-automation/</guid>
      <description>Infrastructure as Code (IaC) has gotten a lot of attention recently. It uses code to manage the configuration and automation of your application’s infrastructure in order to free up resources and reduce risk, technical debt, and mistakes. IaC is becoming more and more important for successful DevOps practices. As a cross-platform infrastructure tool, HashiCorp’s Terraform enables you to automate your infrastructure using the same tooling over multiple platforms. Ansible can be used to build and manage remote application configurations and VM installations on top of your Terraform infrastructure deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serverless Computing: Hot or Not?</title>
      <link>/blog/erverless-computing-hot-or-not-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/erverless-computing-hot-or-not-2/</guid>
      <description>There has been a remarkable increase in serverless computing platforms over the past few years. While few production-ready solutions have been released, the ecosystem has nonetheless matured substantially. You may even have some immediate use cases in your environment or pipeline to consider for a serverless deployment.
Serverless architecture allows web application logic to be processed independently of physical servers, virtual machines, containers, or operating systems. It frees the entity owning the computing system from the obligation to purchase, rent, or obtain servers or virtual machines for the back-end code to run on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Things CloudOps is Betting on in 2018…</title>
      <link>/blog/setting-the-stage-for-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/setting-the-stage-for-2018/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is Betting on 2018! Here’s how.
We continue to race into an ‘everything as a service’ world. The pace is accelerating and the stakes are intensifying. Success in a cloudy world requires software defined operations: end-to-end automation, data collection of all potentially relevant metrics, and smart algorithms that apply predictive analytics (or even machine learning) to ‘big’ data for decision making and hypothesis testing. In 2018, virtuous cycles of lean and agile will operate more closely with computers in the loop leaving humans with the role of steering and supervising like air traffic controllers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native Meetup: K8s 1.9 Update, Lyft’s Migration to Envoy, and Cilium Networking</title>
      <link>/blog/lyfts-migration-to-envoy-1-9-update-cilium-networking-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/lyfts-migration-to-envoy-1-9-update-cilium-networking-meetup/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps hosted an exciting event last night at the Centre cloud.ca in Montreal bringing in speakers from Seattle and Silicon Valley. The event included a 1.9 release update, and presentations on Lyft’s migration to Envoy, and Cilium Network Security. It was the first Kubernetes meetup of the year, and was the meetup that saw Kubernetes integrate into the broader Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) mission.
Our very own Ayrat Kharetdinov was announced as a CNCF ambassador to continue his work expanding the open source community in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost at Sea: Navigating the Complexities of Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/blog/lost-at-sea-navigating-the-complexities-of-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/lost-at-sea-navigating-the-complexities-of-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>A Comparative Summary of Kubernetes Tooling: Open Source, Distributions, and Managed ServicesNote. This blog post was last updated on January 8th, 2019.
Click here to view this blog post as an infographic.
While the efficiency and long-term viability of Kubernetes are apparent, it has a reputation for complexity. To that end, CloudOps has compiled a summary of the best known tools for managing Kubernetes clusters. Facilitating the deployment of containers at scale, Kubernetes allows application design to be standardized into modular and portable microservices that can be easily deployed over multiple cloud environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Containerizing ONAP for Efficiency: Why Bell created OOM using Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/blog/containerizing-onap-for-efficiency-why-bell-created-oom-using-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/containerizing-onap-for-efficiency-why-bell-created-oom-using-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Companies determined to stay digitally relevant are adopting software-centric architectures. Many are transitioning their IT departments from VMs to containers in order to orchestrate workloads in an agile fashion. Although VMs have brought some degree of agility and flexibility by abstracting the computer system into virtual machine images, they also bring with them some of the limitations of traditional operating system (OS) per VM, such as their resource-heavy and monolithic architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is a Kubernetes Certified Service Provider</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-is-a-kubernetes-certified-service-provider/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-is-a-kubernetes-certified-service-provider/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to announce that we are now a Kubernetes Certified Service Provider (KCSP). Run by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation in collaboration with the Linux Foundation, the KCSP program is comprised of 28 vetted service providers with substantial experience helping enterprises adopt Kubernetes successfully. KCSP partners provide support, consulting, and professional services and training for organizations seeking to embrace container solutions. As the only partner in Canada, CloudOps works with partners internationally, and with the CNCF to create a strong and vibrant Kubernetes culture that supports an array of complementary platforms, and fosters the community built around it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security and Resiliency for SaaS Companies</title>
      <link>/blog/security-and-resiliency-for-saas-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/security-and-resiliency-for-saas-companies/</guid>
      <description>It’s neither a secret nor a surprise that security is a growing problem for SaaS companies, which cumulatively possess a tremendous amount of data. Having been proclaimed the new oil, the personal information of customers has become an extremely valuable commodity and this grabs the attention of hackers. Every day, new vulnerabilities are uncovered and malicious attacks are launched at a rate that is difficult to keep up with. In addition to securing data, applications must develop resiliency in order to keep downtime to a minimum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Ranks No. 305 on the 2017 PROFIT 500</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-ranks-305-on-2017-profit-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-ranks-305-on-2017-profit-500/</guid>
      <description>– Canadian Business unveils 29th annual list of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies –
Montreal, QC (September 14, 2017) Canadian Business and PROFIT today ranked CloudOps No. 305 on the 29th annual PROFIT 500, the definitive ranking of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies. Published in the October issue of MacClean’s magazine and at CanadianBusiness.com, the PROFIT 500 ranks Canadian businesses by their five-year revenue growth.
CloudOps made the 2017 PROFIT 500 list with five-year revenue growth of 193%, up from position 356 from last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership with NetApp Propels CloudMC and cloud.ca</title>
      <link>/blog/partnership-with-netapp-propels-cloudmc-and-cloud-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/partnership-with-netapp-propels-cloudmc-and-cloud-ca/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce that CloudOps and NetApp have solidified a partnership that will provide all-flash, multi-tiered storage for our IaaS portal, CloudMC. CloudMC is CloudOps’ software for productizing and delivering cloud resources for telcos and shared services providers. The goal of having such high quality storage as part of our solution is to facilitate scalability, performance, and QoS for organizations leveraging CloudMC to monetize their cloud offering. The key advantages are APIs and automation to make the integration rapid and seamless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker and Kubernetes: What is the Value of Containerization?</title>
      <link>/blog/docker-and-kubernetes-what-is-the-value-of-containerization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/docker-and-kubernetes-what-is-the-value-of-containerization/</guid>
      <description>In the last few years, containerization and microservices-based architecture took the DevOps community by storm. According to 451 Research, container technology such as Docker and Kubernetes will see the fastest growth compared to other cloud-enabling technologies, with an estimated CAGR of 40% through 2020 (see Figure 1). “Two things stand out from our market sizing and research on containers: the breadth and diversity of vendors basing their offerings on containers or integrating and partnering to better support containers in their products and the speed at which the container software and market are maturing based on production, use and revenue growth,” said Greg Zwakman, Vice President, Market and Competitive Intelligence at 451 Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Certified as a Remarkable Employer</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-certified-as-a-remarkable-employer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-certified-as-a-remarkable-employer/</guid>
      <description>As CloudOps grows and matures as a business we look for ways to measure employee satisfaction, both as a means to understand the needs of the people who work here and as a means of comparison with the wider industry. To this end we commissioned Groupe Ambition to conduct their independent certification program. Through an organizational survey of their own design, they have assessed the quality of our internal business relationships as perceived by our employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps and Datera Announce Apache CloudStack Integration for Web-Scale Storage Service</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-datera-apache-cloudstack-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-datera-apache-cloudstack-integration/</guid>
      <description>Software-Defined, Automated, Shared Storage Infrastructure Made Accessible to Open Source CloudStack Community
 CloudOps’ Expertise
Since 2005, CloudOps has focused on delivering vendor-agnostic cloud services with open source at its core. Companies who wish to take advantage of cloud infrastructure for various reasons including agility, elasticity, reliability, and right-sizing of infrastructure have benefitted greatly from CloudOps’ technical and business expertise in delivering cloud solutions.
Apache CloudStack (ACS) has been a major part of CloudOps’ open source IaaS offering to companies who wish to create both private and public cloud deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Ranks No. 356 on the 2016 PROFIT 500</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-ranks-profit-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-ranks-profit-500/</guid>
      <description>– PROFIT magazine unveils 28th annual list of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies –
Montreal, QC (September 15, 2016) Canadian Business and PROFIT today ranked CloudOps No. 356 on the 28th annual PROFIT 500, the definitive ranking of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies. Published in the October issue of Canadian Business and at PROFITguide.com, the PROFIT 500 ranks Canadian businesses by their five-year revenue growth.
CloudOps made the 2016 PROFIT 500 list with five-year revenue growth of 142%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right OpenStack Distribution</title>
      <link>/blog/choosing-the-right-openstack-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/choosing-the-right-openstack-distribution/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack has generated phenomenal mindshare among traditional IT vendors, and has succeeded in capturing the attention of enterprise, telecom and software companies alike. As its operational capabilities have matured in the last few releases, use cases are moving beyond dev/test into production. Therefore, choosing the right implementation and support partners in a large and confusing OpenStack ecosystem is on the minds of many end users, especially considering the likely market winners and losers, and resulting consolidation that is likely to happen in the coming years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Releases Names of Sponsors for Apache CloudStack™ Collab Conference</title>
      <link>/blog/sponsorship-for-apache-cloudstack-collab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sponsorship-for-apache-cloudstack-collab/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 27th 2016:CloudOps is excited to announce the sponsors for #ccc2016mtl. With their support, this event will successfully bring together the community in a robust gathering with multiple avenues for collaboration, discussion and creativity. This Collab is a grassroots event, bringing together this community after a year of immense change. The sponsors of the Collab have had an important role in shaping the content of the event, as well as being integral to the success of the Apache CloudStack project as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Will Stevens As The New Apache™ CloudStack Vice-President</title>
      <link>/blog/will-stevens-apache-cloudstack-vice-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/will-stevens-apache-cloudstack-vice-president/</guid>
      <description>Friday, May 27th 2016:CloudOps is excited to announce that Will Stevens, Lead Developer at CloudOps, has been named as the new Vice-President of the Apache CloudStack project. At the ASF meeting on May 18th, the board passed the resolution appointing Stevens to this position.
CloudOps makes this announcement with the full support and enthusiasm of the entire team and community. Stevens played a central role moving forward on the 4.9 release management duties, and is actively working to improve Apache CloudStack Github-based workflow and continuous integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Announces IDC Vendor Profile</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-announces-idc-vendor-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-announces-idc-vendor-profile/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps is pleased to announce that IDC has created a vendor profile which gives a unique glimpse into a company experiencing phenomenal growth. CloudOps is poised, as the report concludes, to continue its expansion in the market over the next few years.
International Data Corporation (IDC) leads the world in providing market research and intelligence as well as advisory services to the IT market. IDC aids individuals and businesses in making “fact-based decisions” on strategic decisions and market growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps is Named One of Canada’s Top ICT Companies by Branham300</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-branham300/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-branham300/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, April 20th 2016: CloudOps is named one of Canada’s top ICT companies by Branham300, ranking at 221 on this year’s list of Canada’s most-profitable companies. This recognition comes at a pivotal time for CloudOps, as it is poised for hyper growth over the next year. CloudOps is thrilled to be recognized for its growth and profitability even as it accelerates its investment in the next generation of cloud computing solutions for software companies, telecom, and enterprise shared services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps to host Apache CloudStack Collab June 1-3 2016</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-to-host-apache-cloudstack-collab-june-1-3-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-to-host-apache-cloudstack-collab-june-1-3-2016/</guid>
      <description>For Immediate Release
CloudOps Announces Early-Bird Pricing for Apache CloudStack™ Collab Conference for June 2016 #ccc2016mtl CloudOps is excited to host the first Apache CloudStack™ Collab conference of 2016 on June 1-3 2016 in beautiful Montreal, Canada. This conference is aimed at developers, operators and users to discuss and evolve the open source software project, its functionality and real world operability. Part talks, part workshops, part hackathon, this event will present a great opportunity for attendees and sponsors alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supplemental Pack for XenServer allows for VDI per LUN Functionality</title>
      <link>/blog/vdi-per-lun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/vdi-per-lun/</guid>
      <description>Supplemental Pack for XenServer 6.5 Allows VVOLs-like VDI per LUN Functionality for XenServer and Enables Multi-tenant QoS
Syed Ahmed of CloudOps has completed an open source project to allow XenServer 6.5 to leverage backend SAN snapshots by resignaturing metadata of a copied LUN (Logical Unit Number).
This allows more efficient support of processes that rely on snapshots including backups of XenServer virtual machines by leveraging integrated snapshots on a SAN, in this case SolidFire which is a popular scale-out iSCSI block storage for cloud infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Cloud Operations Manifesto</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>Cloud computing is a revolutionary new model for IT services delivery, allowing on-demand utility consumption that can be fully automated via software. Being able to obtain IT resources like hailing a taxi is an essential characteristic of cloud computing. With such new capabilities, cloud computing enables completely new business models, such as e-commerce flash crowd sales (e.g. Beyond the Rack) and massively parallelized compute work (e.g. modelling drug interactions) while enabling us to improve on old business models, allowing for better, faster and cheaper services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Partners with Mirantis</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-partners-with-mirantis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-partners-with-mirantis/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack has dominated conversations in the cloud computing industry for some time as the open source foundation receives funding, code contributions and support from many important players in the space. More than 20 distinct OpenStack projects have been launched in the last 5 years. 
At CloudOps, we are strong supporters of open source communities, contributing to both OpenStack and Apache CloudStack projects. Our CEO, Ian Rae, often compares the two technologies to Playmobil vs Lego; basically that with Playmobil you have a kit of pre-molded parts which allow you to get to play almost right away, whereas Lego lets you customize down to the individual bricks of the infrastructure…and while Lego takes longer to build, it can also be re-configured to meet changing needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Named One of Deloitte’s Technology Fast 50TM Companies</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-named-one-of-deloittes-technology-fast-50tm-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-named-one-of-deloittes-technology-fast-50tm-companies/</guid>
      <description>Montreal, November 12, 2015 — CloudOps is named as one of Canada’s fastest growing technology companies in the 18th annual Deloitte Technology Fast&amp;nbsp;50TM&amp;nbsp;awards for demonstrating bold innovation, dedicated leadership and strong growth. CloudOps ranked 40 with 207 percent in revenue growth from 2011 to 2014. This is the second consecutive year that CloudOps has been ranked.
The Deloitte Technology Fast&amp;nbsp;50TM&amp;nbsp;program celebrates leaders in the Canadian technology industry and tracks the successful growth of Canadian-grown leaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps CEO Featured in KPMG’s The Next Million</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-ceo-featured-in-kpmgs-the-next-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-ceo-featured-in-kpmgs-the-next-million/</guid>
      <description>CloudOps CEO, Ian Rae, was featured in KPMG Canada’s quarterly edition of The Next Million, a magazine about Canadian entrepreneurship. The issue’s theme is cloud computing and companies that have successfully leveraged the cloud to scale their software applications, e-commerce sites, and employee mobility. 
Rae, as a leading figure in the Canadian and international cloud computing space, is being called a “cloud creator.” &amp;nbsp;He founded CloudOps ten years ago and the company has tripled in size in the last three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Ranks No. 204 on the 2015 PROFIT 500</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-ranks-no-204-on-the-2015-profit-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-ranks-no-204-on-the-2015-profit-500/</guid>
      <description>– PROFIT magazine unveils 27thannual list of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies –
Montreal, QC (September 17, 2015) Canadian Businessand PROFIT today ranked CloudOps No. 204 on the 27thannual PROFIT 500, the definitive ranking of Canada’s Fastest-Growing Companies. Published in the October issue of Canadian Businessand at PROFITguide.com, the PROFIT 500 ranks Canadian businesses by their five-year revenue growth. 
CloudOps made the 2015 PROFIT 500 list with five-year revenue growth of 300%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudStack vs. OpenStack: Is There Really a Winner?</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudstack-vs-openstack-is-there-really-a-winner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudstack-vs-openstack-is-there-really-a-winner/</guid>
      <description>About two years ago, I wrote a blog post&amp;nbsp;about my personal experience with the main differences between CloudStack and OpenStack. Since both technologies have evolved, I feel it’s time to take another stab at answering this commonly recurring question : “Should I deploy CloudStack or OpenStack in my organization?”
My first deployments of OpenStack were performed manually and it was really painful. The barrier to entry for deploying such a cloud solution probably discouraged many excellent sysadmins from trying it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudOps Becomes the First Canadian Citrix Specialist in Networking for Data Centre</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudops-becomes-the-first-canadian-citrix-specialist-in-networking-for-data-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudops-becomes-the-first-canadian-citrix-specialist-in-networking-for-data-centre/</guid>
      <description>As Citrix launches its new partner specialist program, CloudOps receives prestigious designation
MONTREAL – CloudOps, a&amp;nbsp;cloud solutions provider and Citrix Gold Partner, announces its most recent Citrix certification as a Networking for Data Centre specialist. The specialization provides a framework for partners to demonstrate technical competency, end-to-end sales capability and service delivery expertise.
The new certification program was announced in early 2015 and allows for a partner to highlight their investments and expertise in a solutions category; virtualization, mobility, or networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting vs. Cloud &amp; Humans vs. Machines</title>
      <link>/blog/hosting-vs-clouds-humans-vs-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hosting-vs-clouds-humans-vs-machines/</guid>
      <description>As VP of Sales and Marketing at CloudOps, I am often explaining the difference between cloud and hosting. My goal is to effectively guide clients to get the maximum business value out of cloud infrastructure services. The greatest business value from cloud is the business agility and efficiency it can enable. I have laid out four items I would want to know if I were starting to use cloud.
Continuously right-size ITWith cloud, you are only paying for what you need, when you need it, instead of wasting money on unused capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Infor and NetSuite Get “Cloud” So Wrong?</title>
      <link>/blog/can-infor-and-netsuite-get-cloud-so-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/can-infor-and-netsuite-get-cloud-so-wrong/</guid>
      <description>This article might be a good example of why software as a service (SaaS) should not be called “cloud.” Equating a subscription software delivery model to cloud masks its&amp;nbsp;true value.
http://diginomica.com/2014/11/12/infor-hits-back-criticism-decision-use-aws-cloudsuite/
Let’s start with the old analogy of comparing cloud computing to an electrical utility. NetSuite is adamant that building and maintaining its own power plants is important, when what customers really value is their software.
Also, the author of the article appears to be saying that Infor requires that its clients use Amazon Web Services (AWS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving To Your New SaaSy Reality</title>
      <link>/blog/moving-to-your-new-saasy-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/moving-to-your-new-saasy-reality/</guid>
      <description>Moving to SaaS isn’t easy. But move you must. And if you make the transition, you’ll care about new things:
Different metrics will matter: Moz began by looking at traffic and churn, but today measures the number of net customers added (“net adds”) and the time it takes to pay back the cost of customer acquisition (“customer payback.”) These numbers aren’t closely scrutinized in a licensing model; in SaaS they’re front and center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Software Is a Four Letter Word</title>
      <link>/blog/the-future-of-software-is-a-four-letter-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-future-of-software-is-a-four-letter-word/</guid>
      <description>There are many reasons the future of software is service-based.THE JOURNEY FROM ISV TO ASP TO SAAS…continued!
Economic motivationsOne of the most tempting things about SaaS is that it generates recurring revenues, As long as you deliver a valuable product and avoid customer churn, you build a “war chest” of future revenues that increases the value of the company. You don’t have to re-sell customers every purchase cycle. Clients aren’t depreciating your license over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How SaaSy Is Your Organization?</title>
      <link>/blog/how-saasy-is-your-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-saasy-is-your-organization/</guid>
      <description>Ultimately, switching from ISV to SaaS means switching from a strict development role to one of development and operations. This isn’t just writing new code, it’s retooling the organization.
Security is no longer about making sure that the codebase is private and virus-free; it’s ensuring that production servers don’t get hacked and that support personnel are briefed against social engineering.
Payment moves from the finance department to become an operational concern involving gateways and automation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fight Is Over, and SaaS Has Won</title>
      <link>/blog/the-fight-is-over-and-saas-has-won/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-fight-is-over-and-saas-has-won/</guid>
      <description>The fight is over, and Software-As-A-Service won. Software companies that wait too long to move to an on-demand model lose market share, and quickly grow out of touch with their customers.Those are some pretty bold statements…especially if you are an ISV.
THE JOURNEY FROM ISV TO ASP TO SAAS
Since the dawn of computing, there has always been a&amp;nbsp;tension between centralized computing and computing&amp;nbsp;at the edge. Mainframes were centrally managed,&amp;nbsp;but as processing became cheaper, they gave way to&amp;nbsp;minicomputers and servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudStack 4.3 API Visualization</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudstack-4-3-api-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudstack-4-3-api-visualization/</guid>
      <description>Click the image to interact with the visualization…..
I put together a visualization of the CloudStack API based on the public documentation. &amp;nbsp;This visualization represents the request references from basic entities to other basic entities. &amp;nbsp;The arrow direction is the direction in which the reference is made. So if an API call in the Virtual Machine section references a Network, it would appear as: Virtual Machine-&amp;gt; Network. I am not showing the specific API calls, I am grouping all the API calls for a section together and mapping them to other logical sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing cloud.ca – enterprise cloud in Canada</title>
      <link>/blog/announcing-cloud-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/announcing-cloud-ca/</guid>
      <description>We’ve spent much of the past few years helping to design and deploy both private and public clouds internationally, largely atop the Citrix CloudPlatform architecture and the most operationally mature open source technologies available from the CloudStack and OpenStack projects. With this experience under our belts, we’re taking the cover off something significant: our own secure multi-tenant cloud.
The cloud landscape has changed significantly, and now clouds are an essential tool in the IT toolbox—and Canadians deserve these tools close at hand to maintain data sovereignty and comply with privacy regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parlons-en Cloud 2014: some topics</title>
      <link>/blog/parlons-en-cloud-2014-some-topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/parlons-en-cloud-2014-some-topics/</guid>
      <description>Next week, Stephan Bureau and I will join a few hundred IT professionals from Québec for a day-long conference on cloud computing. We’re tackling three big themes, with panelists from both vendors and end-users, spanning small and large businesses as well as governments.
The three themes are at the forefront of technology policy today:
Transition and migrationCloud computing is a major shift for IT. It is a switch from capex to opex; from ownership to rental; and from infrastructure engineering to service design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researching cloud adoption</title>
      <link>/blog/researching-cloud-adoption/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/researching-cloud-adoption/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a few years since clouds were new. Today, utility computing is a tool in the IT toolbox, and it consists of both on-premise and on-demand components. We have strong private stacks (Cloud Platform, OpenStack, Eucalyptus, VMWare and others) and a variety of large-scale public providers at both the IaaS (Amazon, Google Compute Engine, Rackspace) and PaaS (Cloud Foundry, Openshift, App Engine, Heroku) level.
Yet there are still plenty of reasons why companies fail to embrace clouds, from governance and compliance concerns to questions around performance and cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clouds are like airlines</title>
      <link>/blog/clouds-are-like-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/clouds-are-like-airlines/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve read Nic Carr’s book The Big Switch, you’ll have heard the analogy that cloud computing is like eletricity: we’re moving from computers to computing, just as we moved from generators to generation.
Certainly, clouds (at least, big public ones like Amazon Web Services and Google Compute Engine) have a lot in common with an electrical utility. They’re elastic, because you can change your demand and pay for what you use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudStack: Creating advanced networking zone using API</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudstack-creating-advanced-networking-zone-using-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudstack-creating-advanced-networking-zone-using-api/</guid>
      <description>In the process of automating CloudStack installation, we’ve been through a challenging part: Creating an Entire Advanced networking Zone from the API. Production and test system that we deploy don’t have building tools such as mavin in order to create zones, pod,networks,… So the usual process is to use the Web UI and follow the “Add Zone” wizard. Well, not anymore!
To create an entire zone using API we are using Ruby with Chip’s cloudstack_ruby_client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Cloud(Ops) Story</title>
      <link>/blog/a-cloudops-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/a-cloudops-story/</guid>
      <description>As a web operations firm in 2005, we were privileged to experience the emergence of cloud computing. At the time, our customers were exclusively e-commerce, SaaS, and advertising-driven publishing businesses. Amazon Web Services (AWS) unlocked what was essentially an unsolved problem — how to right-size your infrastructure to meet the needs of your business — and our AWS solutions provided our customers with just-in-time (JIT) infrastructure.
Most folks outside the industry are unaware that what started as an online bookstore is leading a revolution in computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the cloud is (and needs to be) like Minecraft</title>
      <link>/blog/why-the-cloud-is-and-needs-to-be-like-minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-the-cloud-is-and-needs-to-be-like-minecraft/</guid>
      <description>by Pierre-Luc Bisaillon If&amp;nbsp;you have a young kid (or are a kid at heart), Minecraft doesn’t need any introduction. At last count 10M people had bought the game and at least 5 times as many are playing the demo or some mobile version. For the uninitiated, this seems odd. The graphics are awful, and it’s not even a real “game” – in other words, there’s no mission or objective to achieve and “win”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Apache Cloudstack with Chef</title>
      <link>/blog/install-apache-cloudstack-with-chef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/install-apache-cloudstack-with-chef/</guid>
      <description>Installation of Apache CloudStack and is dependencies using Opscode Chef&amp;nbsp;community cookbooks.
To create a lab, a test environment or to just try CloudStack, you could install it using the installation documentation which is clean and fairly straight forward, but you can also install it with Chef and not worry about subtleties. Here is a quick way of installing CloudStack, MySQL server and NFS service into a single server to provide what’s required to setup a CloudStack lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get a job in the cloud industry</title>
      <link>/blog/how-to-get-a-job-in-the-cloud-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-to-get-a-job-in-the-cloud-industry/</guid>
      <description>by Pierre-Luc Bisaillon
After a few weeks of career days, wine and cheese, and interviews, I wanted to summarize a few key findings and give some tips to students (and grown-ups) looking for a job with CloudOps — or anywhere in the cloud industry, for that matter.
Try AWS — for free
Amazon Web Services is the industry leader and has enough capacity to offer every new customer a free tier, which enables you to get an amount of resources on the public cloud service for free, including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudStack vs. OpenStack: My Experience</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudstack-vs-openstack-a-personal-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudstack-vs-openstack-a-personal-experience/</guid>
      <description>by François Gaudreault
Before anyone starts to rant or panic, a few disclaimers:
 We love both CloudStack and OpenStack. In fact, we wrote and shared a connector to allow OpenStack Swift to authenticate against CloudStack.We are a Citrix CloudAdvisor and have deep expertise with the Citrix CloudPlatform and Cloud Portal Business Manager products, and by extension, CloudStack.We want to continue to provide our customers with the best solutions on the market to achieve their business goals as fast as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up an Ideal CloudStack Development Environment</title>
      <link>/blog/setting-up-an-ideal-cloudstack-development-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/setting-up-an-ideal-cloudstack-development-environment/</guid>
      <description>In this, my first article, I answer a question that I often get asked: How do I set up and prepare my development environment for CloudStack? True, there are many articles and wiki pages available on this subject, but here is my method.
Keep in mind that this article assumes a good knowledge of Linux. It is intended for developers who want to try out the latest development environment on their workstation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Web Application Firewalls</title>
      <link>/blog/thinking-about-web-application-firewalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/thinking-about-web-application-firewalls/</guid>
      <description>Web Application Firewalls (WAFs) are growing in the market, providing many benefits including the prevention zero-day exploits.
What is a Web Application Firewall?
By definition, a web application firewall is a device that sits between the client and the web server and analyses layer 7 messages for violations in the defined security policy. In other words, WASFs look at HTTP/HTTPS/SOAP/XML requests and responses and look for potential attacks according to predefined rules on the device or abnormal behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with the CloudStack API</title>
      <link>/blog/working-with-the-cloudstack-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/working-with-the-cloudstack-api/</guid>
      <description>The CloudStack API is a very powerful tool for managing your infrastructure and is often not utilized to its full potential. I think this is mainly due to the initial learning curve to get working with the API. In this post I will present the basics you will need to start using the API as well as provide working examples to get you started.
The first potential stumbling block is the method for accessing the API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Consider Commercially Supported Open Source</title>
      <link>/blog/why-you-should-consider-commercially-supported-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-you-should-consider-commercially-supported-open-source/</guid>
      <description>While open source technologies such as Linux and Apache are making inroads into larger companies, the thought of using open source technologies in a production environment will still cause most CIOs to lose sleep. Add to that the thought of using open source in the context of the Cloud and that poor CIO many never sleep another wink! The combination of open source with the Cloud is simply too risky for most enterprise CIOs today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Citrix NetScaler from Cisco ACE? CloudOps Can Help</title>
      <link>/blog/migrating-to-citrix-netscaler-from-cisco-ace-cloudops-can-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/migrating-to-citrix-netscaler-from-cisco-ace-cloudops-can-help/</guid>
      <description>This month, Cisco announced via a press release that it will recommend and integrate Citrix Systems’ NetScaler application delivery controller. The move follows an earlier announcement by Cisco that it was scaling down work on the company’s ACE load balancer. The partnership with Citrix, which will see Cisco actively recommend Citrix NetScaler to its customers is a move to close the gap, and provide Cisco ACE users with a solid future path and a Cisco-approved migration option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Striking the Balance Between Innovation and Standardization in Cloud-Based Development</title>
      <link>/blog/striking-the-balance-between-innovation-and-standardization-in-cloud-based-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/striking-the-balance-between-innovation-and-standardization-in-cloud-based-development/</guid>
      <description>One of the key principles of Cloud-based development is that everything in that development environment – including the infrastructure — is offered to the user (developer) as a service.
In this new world, you don’t give a development team a server, or a load-balancing device. You give developers access to a storage service and a load-balancing service. Leading cloud providers, public or private, offer a wide array of computing, networking, storage, authentication, database, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is your favourite cloud computing quote?</title>
      <link>/blog/what-is-your-favourite-cloud-computing-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what-is-your-favourite-cloud-computing-quote/</guid>
      <description>Quotes are a simple yet powerful to illustrate and distil a more complicated idea or concept. So I was amused when I read these 5 cloud computing quotes, including internet pioneer Marc Andreessen. A quick search also revealed some good ones here.
My favourite quote is probably one I heard at INTEROP Las Vegas last spring: “Stop thinking about your servers as pets, and start thinking about them as cattle.” Although slightly harsh, it illustrates that cloud computing requires a completely new level of thinking when it comes to managing the infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About CloudOps | Own Your Destiny in the Cloud™</title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Meet CloudOps   CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking, and DevOps.       History Launched in 2005 by Ian Rae to meet the infrastructure needs of software-focused organizations, CloudOps has grown steadily and organically from an operations managed services shop to a leader in cloud computing, cloud networking, and DevOps solutions. The services we provide help customers use and build cloud platforms, with an emphasis on operational success and networking connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Docker and Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/advanced-docker-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-docker-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     Advanced Docker and Kubernetes CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
 Day to day operations and best practices around Kubernetes; Concepts around HA, securing, logging and monitoring of Kubernetes.  This workshop is available on Azure, GCP and AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careers</title>
      <link>/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/</guid>
      <description>Careers   CloudOps is a company at the leading edge of the ever-changing cloud industry. Our growing Team of Teams gets the unique chance to work with, learn, and collaborate on the best tools and platforms in the market.      Join the CloudOps Team of Teams Whether you are fascinated by new cloud technologies, passionate about finding the best solution for a customer’s problem, or driven by getting hands-on into the code, CloudOps and its affiliated companies, have a wide variety of career paths to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD Training</title>
      <link>/ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     CI / CD CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
 Tools and best practices to build, test, and ship software as well as enhance and automate your delivery pipeline.  Duration: 1 day
On Premise: $1500/attendee (minimum 6 attendees)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CKA &amp; CKAD Exams</title>
      <link>/cka-ckad-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cka-ckad-exams/</guid>
      <description>CKA &amp; CKAD Exams      CKA exam Certification is a key step in developing the Kubernetes ecosystem and for professional growth. The exam is based on the latest version of Kubernetes and issued by the CNCF and the Linux Foundation. CloudOps&#39; 3-day Docker and Kubernetes workshop plus one day exam prep (focused on operations) will get you certification ready!
The CKA exam covers:
  Application Lifecycle Management 8% Installation, Configuration &amp; Validation Core Concepts Networking Scheduling    Security Cluster Maintenance Logging / Monitoring Storage Troubleshooting      CKAD exam This exam is for developers who design, build, configure, and expose cloud native applications for Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Migration</title>
      <link>/cloud-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloud-migration/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Migration    Migrating workloads to the cloud doesn’t have to be overwhelming. CloudOps will partner with you to plan your move step-by-step, execute it with care, and set you up for operational success.       You&#39;re ready to move to the cloud. You understand the business advantages that come with a cloud operational model. The wider market does too. In fact, this year some 83% of enterprise workloads will already be in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native Consulting</title>
      <link>/cloud-native-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cloud-native-consulting/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Native Consulting   Speed up your cloud native project with CloudOps’ expert advice and implementation. We help you navigate the ever-changing cloud native landscape to find the best solutions for your needs.      Getting to cloud native A cloud native application is built to live in the cloud. It auto-provisions, auto-scales, and is auto-resilient, delivering maximum value to a business and its end users. The more successfully an application lives in the cloud without causing lock-in to one provider, the more cloud native it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Contact Us     Let&#39;s talk! We can help you on your journey with the cloud.
Contact us using the form below and someone from our team will get back to you within the next business day.
    hbspt.forms.create({ portalId: &#34;732832&#34;, formId: &#34;5ea8cd78-739b-4936-97b8-973ec0dc01ee&#34; });   1-514-447-3456 (Montreal) 1-855-652-5683 (toll-free) 1-514-312-5288 (fax)  info@cloudops.com    Our Offices  Montreal (Head Office) 200-423 rue Saint-Nicolas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Cloud</title>
      <link>/delivering-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/delivering-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Delivering Cloud CloudOps enables telecoms and managed service providers to deliver and monetize cloud and network service offerings with certified expertise, training, and CloudMC – an Edge Orchestration Platform.       Today’s telecom service providers are looking for new ways to grow revenue. Meanwhile, the enterprise service market has a growing need for integrated commercial offerings that include: edge computing, cloud native technologies, hybrid multi-cloud infrastructures, data sovereign storage solutions, SD-WAN, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Cloud Consulting</title>
      <link>/delivering-cloud-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/delivering-cloud-consulting/</guid>
      <description>Delivering Cloud Consulting    CloudOps helps empower telecoms and MSPs in their delivery and monetization of differentiated cloud and network service offerings.       A changing landscape Telecoms are only seeing modest growth prospects for their traditional lines of business. Where hosting customer workloads was once enough, today’s enterprise IT users want integrated commercial offerings that include: edge computing, cloud native technologies, hybrid multi-cloud infrastructures, data sovereign storage solutions, SD-WAN, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Monitoring Workshop</title>
      <link>/devops-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/devops-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     DevOps Monitoring CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     In this workshop, we explore app and infrastructure monitoring tools (open source and not), configurations, APM, altering and visualizing data with hands-on labs.
Duration: 2 days
On Premise: $2500/attendee (minimum 6 attendees)
 Prerequisites: Experience using Linux CLI and a general understanding of DevOps concepts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Platform and Practices Assessment</title>
      <link>/dppa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dppa/</guid>
      <description>DevOps Platform and Practices Assessment      Whether your team already works in a DevOps manner or if you are just beginning the journey, CloudOps can help pave the way. We provide an objective report of the application portfolio, business impact, technical risks, and the path (and gaps) to DevOps best practices and cloud native development and delivery.      Who is it for?: Organizations evaluating cloud platforms DevOps teams looking to maximize efficiency Any organizations who run business critical applications, who care about speed to market and modernization of their applications, and looking to adopt DevOps        Understand the real issues Our assessment report provides suggested scope of any next steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker and Kubernetes Workshop</title>
      <link>/docker-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docker-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     Docker and Kubernetes CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     CloudOps’ flagship workshop covers architecture principles of microservices, then gets in to the mechanics of container tooling – now a key model for application development.
Our workshops are Linux-based. If you are interested in Docker and Kubernetes training on Windows, please let us know here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker and Kubernetes Workshop</title>
      <link>/infrastructure-as-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/infrastructure-as-code/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     Infrastructure as Code CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
 How Hashicorp Terraform by Hashicorp works as a cross platform, infrastructure tool enabling you to use the same tooling over multiple platforms for infrastructure automation; How Ansible can be used to manage remote application configurations and VM installations built on top of your Terraform infrastructure deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Solutions for Using the Cloud</title>
      <link>/using-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/using-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Using Cloud   CloudOps helps you define your cloud goals and solve complex problems. We empower your team, regardless of where you are at in your journey and the cloud platforms you use.       Our team solves for the best ways to reach your business, cultural, and technical objectives in using the cloud. Along the way, we equip you with all the knowledge you need to operationalize your technology stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts</title>
      <link>/experts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experts/</guid>
      <description>Our Experts   Our team works tirelessly to build, maintain, and deliver up-to-date, practical content on a variety of subjects and tools.      Our experts    Michael Foster Cloud Solution Architect Michael specializes in cloud native technologies, including Docker and Kubernetes, as well as CI/CD and monitoring tools. He is a Certified Kubernetes Administrator, and has worked on data pipelines and process optimization for organizations ranging from research centres to international banks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning and Kubernetes Workshop</title>
      <link>/kubernetes-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kubernetes-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     Kubernetes and Machine Learning CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
 How to run deployments of machine learning (ML) workflows on Kubernetes to make them simple, portable and scalable with open source tools.  Standalone 2 days: $4,000/attendee (minimum 6 attendees)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managed Services and Augmented Support</title>
      <link>/managed-services-augmented-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/managed-services-augmented-support/</guid>
      <description>Managed Services and Augmented Support   Cloud operations are complex. We&#39;re here to help.      We know you feel it—the pressure to transform your organization digitally, to release new features at a faster pace, to innovate. Software is eating the world and you need to set yourself up to bring software-based solutions to your industry.
The problem? Building and running a DevOps-ready cloud operations team is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monolith to Microservices Workshop</title>
      <link>/monolith-microservices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monolith-microservices/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     Monolith to microservices CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
 How to migrate an existing legacy JavaTM EE app to Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform on OpenShift How to use modern frameworks like Spring Boot, Wildfly Swarm, Eclipse Vert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenShift Workshop</title>
      <link>/openshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openshift/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     OpenShift CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
How to install, administer and use Red Hat OpenShift container platform to deploy your enterprise applications. Duration: 2 or 3 days
Two day OpenShift: $2500/attendee (minimum 6 attendees)
Three day Docker &amp; Kubernetes bundle: $3000/attendee (min.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/</guid>
      <description>Our Partners   CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps      Partners                                                             Memberships and Certifications                         Affiliated companies CloudOps has some special partnerships that we use to provide neighbouring and complementary cloud solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy (Last modified on January 18, 2018)     Introduction, Definitions, Modifications and Acceptance Welcome to CloudOps. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) may cover several different situations, so please refer to the following definitions for clarification:
“CloudOps” refers to CloudOps Inc., a duly incorporated company in the Province of Quebec, Canada. Where the present Policy refers to “CloudOps”, it may refer to CloudOps Inc. and / or its affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, officers, directors, subcontractors, agents, partners or representatives, depending on the context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets Management Workshop</title>
      <link>/secrets-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/secrets-management/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Home  Next Workshop     Secrets Management CloudOps is a cloud consulting, managed services, and software company focused on open source, cloud native platforms, networking and DevOps     During this workshop you will learn:
 How to use Hashicorp Vault as a reliable tool for secrets management and data protection; Operational components and techniques for integrating Vault secrets into applications.  Duration: ½ day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions</title>
      <link>/solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Services and Products   Cloud native technologies and DevOps practices are complex. Modernize existing applications and enable new operational models. We help you throughout your journey.      We partner with our customers to meet business, cultural, and technical requirements. CloudOps prides itself on being platform and tool agnostic but opinionated when building, operating, and equipping teams to support successful cloud strategies. This allows our customers to own their destiny with a mix of open source software, partner, DevOps tools, and our own automation workflows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformations</title>
      <link>/transformations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/transformations/</guid>
      <description>Transformations    Accelerate your transformation to unlock new business models with new technologies. We provide consulting, culture and skills training, and custom blueprints for change.       Whether you’re beginning a digital transformation for the first time or working hard to get it right, we understand the challenges that come with making such a complex set of changes.
CloudOps supports you in a number of transformations: DevOps transformations to innovate at a faster pace, CloudOps transformations to unlock a cloud service provider business model, and DevNetOps transformations to leverage network-as-code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why CloudOps</title>
      <link>/why-cloudops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/why-cloudops/</guid>
      <description>Why CloudOps?         CloudOps helps organizations succeed in the cloud.   When adopting new cloud technologies, it is easy for organizations to get lost down a rabbit hole of searching for the right cloud solutions, attempting to upskill technical teams, changing culture, and defining new lines of business.  Before you know it, your team can be distracted by these new projects, not delivering on your organization’s core business value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Calendar</title>
      <link>/workshops-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops-calendar/</guid>
      <description>Calendar   Our workshops get your team up to speed on DevOps, and cloud native tooling, on any cloud in days—not months.      Workshops  Events   Upcoming Workshops   Docker and Kubernetes CloudOps’ flagship workshop covers architecture principles of microservices, then gets in to the mechanics of container tooling – now a key model for application development.
Course details     July 14-16, 2020 Online   Sign Up     DevOps Monitoring We will explore app and infrastructure monitoring tools (open source and not), configurations, APM, altering and visualizing data with hands-on labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops for DevOps, cloud native, and tooling</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>Upskill your team with CloudOps workshops   Our workshops get your team up to speed on DevOps, and cloud native tooling, on any cloud in days—not months.      Empower your team with our hands-on workshops     Who can benefit?  Developers Operators DevOps practicioners Technical desicion makers    Why attend?  Start using containers in development and production Deliver code faster, more efficiently Deepen your knowledge on specific tools Build technical skills with hands-on workshops Learn the business value of new methods Learn to navigate the complex cloud native ecosystem     Calendar       - Meet our experts -      Michael Foster Cloud Solution Architect      Samira Barouti Cloud Software Architect      Syed Ahmed Lead Cloud Architect     Learn more about our experts       DevOps Workshops  Microservices, Docker &amp; Basic Kubernetes 3 days CloudOps’ flagship workshop covers microservices architecture principles and the mechanics of container tooling; now a key model for application development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>